Hey, everybody.
Man, I'm vibing to this music.
It's so good.
I have to say, I think the Talos principle may contain some of the best music I've ever heard in a video game.
It's definitely among my top three of all time.
Man, every time I hear it, I get transported to a different world.
Ah, it does something to me.
Oh, man.
Have you finished Stanley already?
I have not.
I almost just started.
I think I've played four hours of it so far.
Something like that.
Fucking crazy game.
I love it, though.
Yeah, the piano is nuts.
It's so good.
Rain world is also similar in that way, yeah.
Hey Oliver, did you get the email I sent with the logo animation stuff?
Oh, I haven't checked my email.
Or maybe I have.
Hold on.
Let me see.
I didn't know you sent me an email.
Oh, yeah, I did get it.
Sorry, I haven't read through it all yet.
I'm gonna check that out later.
Thank you so much.
I saw the animation you made on Discord.
Actually amazing.
So good.
I'll definitely be using that at some point.
I was thinking of animating that thing myself because it's just begging to be animated.
Definitely.
Thanks, man.
Yeah, you sent it to the right place.
Thank you.
Also, what should I call you?
Because you have different names everywhere.
What would you prefer to be called?
non zero feet.
Dementia emailing.
Yeah, I have like four different email accounts, so it's kind of hard to keep track.
There's the work email.
There's the play email.
There's the channel email and then there's some old-school email that I never use because it's so old but I still kind of need to use it sometimes because I'm signed up to things with it.
Haha, just email problems.
How y'all doing?
Man, I feel so relaxed.
I was about to say this game, Neuta, is the perfect game for being relaxed, but it kind of isn't.
It's the weirdest mix between a relaxing game and a frustrating game.
But I'm in the middle of a run here.
I'm excited to see where I ended up.
I actually forgot.
RuneScape account forever gone to a 2007 email.
I don't remember anything about.
Relatable.
Dude, Mr. Robot is an incredible show.
You're in for a treat.
You really are.
There are some episodes on that show that when I saw that with my friend, like there's like a little opening sequence at some point and we both looked at each other and went Holy shit, that was good.
Like we were so hyped.
That show was amazing.
Have fun, man.
Rain world in the same manner.
Yeah, it's not relaxing, but it kind of is.
Standing in the rain and listening to the wind, you know, when no animals are nearby.
Just incredible.
And then the action happens and then you have moments of quiet.
And that back and forth is just so good.
Is this the start of the stream?
Yeah, it is.
I just started, Saika.
Welcome.
Vabbitt Raven Warrior gifted us up to Blubpaula.
Blubpaula?
That's the Death Counter guy.
I feel kind of terrible calling you the Death Counter guy.
Blubpaula that is, but I don't know what you would prefer to be called.
Probably just Poli.
Makes me think of the Sopranos though when I say that.
And a bathtub pops out of nowhere?
Exactly.
Looking forward to more Noita.
Hope this run continues to go well and you can find more questions.
Yeah, indeed.
But you should be prepared for me just dying immediately because that can happen in this game and I'm also prepared for that.
I think I have a pretty good run going right now.
I'll have to see where I was, but...
I am mentally prepared to lose everything at any moment.
That's just the way of the Noita.
You finally catch a Noita stream from the start.
It's good to have you Saika 10.
Is your name Saika 10 because Saika 1 through 9 were taken?
Or is it a reference to something?
Non-Aft is fine.
Oh, Aft!
Okay, I thought it was a 0.
I'm not gonna be picky.
Okay, so I'm gonna call you Non-Aft.
That's awesome.
I thought it was 0 feet.
There's a Rainworld announcement in two days?
Really?
But isn't that just the announcement we already know about, about the new Slugcat?
Will you play Rainworld's The Watcher DLC when it comes out?
Oh, that's the Slay the Spire DLC for Rainworld, right?
Where you get to play this ninja?
Where you go into divinity and Wrath mode and all that, right?
Yeah, I'll definitely play that.
I think so at least, yeah.
I'm kidding, guys.
Hey, what's up, Diego?
How you doing?
What's it like having already beaten the Stanley Parable?
Oh, it's amazing.
Yeah, yeah.
I've also never played the game, so that's another thing, but yeah.
So good.
You posted two Neuter gifts in the game's channel.
I ray traced black holes that make them look realistic.
Really?
That sounds like a lot of fun, actually.
I mean, they already look nuts as it is, so...
Incredible.
You're doing good?
Nice.
Glad to hear it.
Hope everything is going well at dark.
You're currently building a rendering engine.
And your plan is to render the logo?
Oh my god.
You guys are obsessed with that logo.
I love it.
I'm kind of impressed that you're making a rendering engine.
That sounds difficult.
I don't know anything about engines.
I'm not a black thumb.
You want to watch the Stanley Parable episode?
Go watch it.
You don't have to be here.
It's okay.
I don't mind.
Go, go, go.
Enjoy it.
As I remember, first few numbers were already taken and I jumped to 10.
Okay.
You're like, ah, fuck it.
Probably nobody has it up to 10.
Yeah.
It's changed a lot.
Hmm.
Okay.
Maybe you'll tell me about it one day.
Is your logo supposed to be an accretion disk?
I mean, yeah, sure.
Honestly, I guess so.
I was just trying to make something look cool.
I guess I had a black hole in mind.
You know, a bit of an accretion disk.
Yeah.
But honestly, I just wanted something that fit with the already existing logo with the white circle.
And I thought, hey, black holes makes sense because I studied black holes back then.
So I'm always asking about username numbers.
I mean, come on.
You can't blame me.
We have an antlers 12 and a 12 antlers.
That's a little bit mysterious to me.
You gotta ask about it.
You can't not ask about that.
It's everything and nothing at the same time.
StylusDead would only work with the little messed up circle.
I have to get that emote on Twitch as well.
The one we made for the t-shirt.
I feel like if it's the full circle, it should be StylusAlive.
And StylusDead is the one where it's kind of like scuffed.
My username have no numbers.
I feel incomplete.
Ah, don't feel incomplete.
So guys, what are your social security numbers?
Aren't you studying something about Sagittarius A?
No, I'm not.
No, nope.
I'm kind of forgetting that from your vlog.
No, I'm not studying anything right now.
Not at this moment.
At the moment, I'm full time, baby.
Full time streamer.
I'm trying it for a year.
I don't know if you caught that announcement.
But it wasn't really an announcement.
I sort of mentioned it offhand in the second last stream I did.
Yeah, now I'm studying gaming.
I study gaming black holes.
Who wants the funny numbers from my mother's credit card?
Why is that sentence so funny?
Oh, man.
Oh, yeah, I'm studying black holes and noise.
That's right.
That's a good one.
How much instant noodles will there be?
Not much, because it's not very good for you in the long run.
I need something substantial.
Probably I'll be eating whole foods a lot.
You know, rice.
Potatoes, of course.
That's a good way to get some nutrition.
I saw realistic black holes, reskin for noise of black holes on Reddit.
It was crazy.
Someone also posted a gif of it on the Discord.
Elimseturkur.
God, I can't pronounce that name.
I'm sorry.
Elimseturkru.
That's it.
Yeah, already full time streamer.
Yeah, give me your credit card numbers.
Broccoli is always good and cheap source.
That's true.
And it's super easy to make in the in the air fryer.
I like to put a bit of oil on it, some salt and some... Oh, what's that, you know, black stuff that you have in that reminds you of oil.
It's like an Italian thing.
But you put that on and the air fryer make it a little crispy.
Oh, so good.
With some salmon as well.
Ooh, you've got a meal.
Essentially false.
Has resubscribed with Prime.
Thank you very much.
That's two months.
That's so demon.
I love that you guys have embraced that so much.
It's become part of the vocabulary here now.
I can't stop laughing every time someone makes something new out of that.
I had no idea that would become that popular.
Balsamic.
That's the one wandering falcon.
Thank you.
Balsamic.
Balsamic?
I don't know how to and I have no idea where I am.
So that's interesting.
We have to reacquaint ourselves with our surroundings and all that.
Also, let me just phase this out.
There we go.
And transition.
Man, I feel like such a professional when I click on the stream deck and I change scenes.
It's amazing.
Oh, and of course.
Cheers, everybody.
Yeah, that was Talos principal music.
Such an incredible soundtrack.
Also, that can opening was false.
It was fake.
I got you all.
There, gotta open four cans in a row.
Now, but I did open a can.
I'm not kidding.
I think I did this joke once before, but it's too funny.
Oh, I'm kidding, guys.
That's funny.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, shit, I'm in the middle of something.
Oh, wait, wait.
Okay, let's see here.
Okay, I've got a machine gun wand.
That makes sense.
That's something I would do.
I remember now, it's vampirism.
Vampirism, oil blood, electricity, immunity.
We gambled, got an always cast one off on one of the wands.
Faster levitation, that's right.
I remember this now.
It was going pretty well.
2,800 monies.
It's not bad.
So hold on, how many perks did I... or how many holy mountains did I visit?
This is these two, so that's one, two, three, four.
So wait, have I gone back up into here?
I must have gone further down and then came back up later.
And I have... what do I have here?
I have unstable teleportation, blood potion.
Oops.
Am I fire immune?
I'm not.
Okay.
Drink a bit of that.
And then we also have levitation.
Okay.
Good, good, good.
Spiders are abound.
I'm not afraid of you guys.
I am afraid of the big ones though.
Yeah, this one is not that much of a machine gun, is it?
It's kind of pathetic.
Definitely need more.
More speed.
Man, it's awkward having the faster levitation.
Okay, he's kind of tanky.
I also got to check what spells I have.
Okay, I have a couple different things.
And I'm immune to electricity, baby!
Feels good.
Wait!
Wait, this guy's hard to kill.
I think I stunned him with my electricity there.
Drink some blood.
Geek at death cross.
Was I keeping this wand for something?
I don't think so.
I'll take that, thanks.
Man, I gotta go up and find the... I actually don't remember if I went up or down, which way I was going last time.
It may as well have been a way up.
I need to double check by going through the portal and see what I was up to.
Got him.
And I can change all the corpses to get some blood here.
Very nice.
Proven technique.
Something they taught me at the vampire academy of 84.
Valuable lessons indeed.
Let's see what we got.
Wait a minute.
I have not been here.
Wait, how does that make sense?
How do I have so many perks?
Oh, oh, wait a minute.
I think I know why.
I'm just not remembering how many or what the order is here.
That's the first two perks here.
Or sorry, I should say here, technically.
And then one more there.
That's three.
Two, three, four, five.
And that's what I have.
One, two, one, two, three.
Yeah, okay, that makes sense.
Perfect.
Oh, that's that's lovely.
So now I know exactly where I'm going.
Projectile Thunderfield.
That sounds interesting now that I'm immune to electricity.
Not exactly sure what that means.
It does say it has six on it, so it's a limited use.
Not too happy about that.
Let's see here.
That's Pinpointer.
That's a good one.
Ooh.
No, wait, I thought this was the immune to explosions.
It's not.
Oh, actually this.
Enemies explode upon death, but you gain immunity to explosive damage.
I wonder if this will fuck my plan regarding drinking blood.
If the corpses explode, I wonder if blood will come out of it or not.
This could be an issue.
Hmm.
Damn.
Revenge explosion.
You release a magical explosion upon taking damage and gain 25% resistance against explosions.
I would rather be immune to explosions.
But then again, Pinpointer is not bad either.
I think I gotta try this.
See how it works with vampirism.
I'm too interested now.
Okay, what's this?
Powder vacuum field.
Okay, I think I want to try this one.
Oh, I need to get rid of some stuff.
Let's get rid of... since I'm immune to explosions, we can maybe do something with this now.
Not a bad idea.
I can get rid of some of these.
This one is not actually bad.
That's actually a decent wand.
Hold on, what do my wands look like here?
Oh, I remember this.
Wait, why is this one so slow?
Oh, it's much faster when you shoot it at a wall next to you than further away.
It's only when this thing explodes at the end or the trigger happens that the wand starts over, you know?
That we went through a recharge.
I like the green glimmer.
That can potentially help me up here.
I do not remember exactly what I'm limited by.
I think it may just be Castellae.
Let me try and put this in here.
Ooh!
Now I remember.
The reason I didn't do this, I had the ability to with this one.
Reduce recharge time.
The reason I didn't do it is because I don't have enough mana.
Right.
I remember now.
Everything's coming back.
Get rid of that one.
I think this electricity sound is going to piss me off in the long run.
I'm not going to lie there.
That's...
Don't enjoy it too much.
I think I'll get rid of that one as well.
Now the circle of shielding sounds cool, but maybe I don't really need it.
I'm sorry, fishes!
I electrocuted them in cold blood.
Okay, let me try and buy this.
Projectiles caught within the field transform into blasts of lightning.
Jesus.
I should be fine.
I'm immunity to explosion and electricity, so I can't go wrong with this.
At least testing it.
Oh really?
Whoo!
Wow!
Oh, that's messed up.
Dude, imagine making something like this at a boss place.
Wait for them to come close and just brrr.
That's going to do insane damage.
Also because when bosses shoot into that, or enemies I guess, all their projectiles are going to be transformed.
And I'm immune to that.
Oh yeah!
I think that's huge.
Triple spell could also come in handy.
I'll take it.
I'm so rich right now.
This one is intriguing.
Powder vacuum field.
Let's see here.
Sucks powder-like materials nearby and releases them upon expiring.
Let me just see that again.
Right.
And how long does it last?
Okay.
Why would I like that?
I'm trying to understand the use case for this.
Hmm.
I really like this one.
Later we can make it infinite.
Either by hopefully a perk or by some spells that we're going to find.
At yalke misti.
But right now I think I'm okay.
All this looks...
I think this one is still decent.
We really need to find some extra mana.
That's the big one.
This one does have a lot of mana max but we need more mana charge.
Oh, this one is horrible actually in that department.
Let's get rid of this one.
And maybe I will put these two on this one instead.
It's not as fast but it doesn't have to be.
I just don't like this wand very much.
We can replace that wand.
Yeah, that seems wise.
I think we move on.
Oh, and wait a minute.
I have teleport.
Can I somehow get out of here?
I forgot what my situation was regarding the holy mountains.
What did I do?
Did I actually do anything regarding that?
I have not angered the gods obviously, otherwise Stuart would be here.
Did I dig somehow?
I don't think I did.
I think I just went on.
Yeah, it seems like that's what I did.
Feels kind of bad honestly.
We're kind of deep now, you know.
But it is what it is.
Dude, we're immune to fire, electricity and explosions.
How crazy is that?
Also, we really need to be a little closer to the enemies before we shoot, because if I hit them before this place right here, you see, where my cursor is, then I do very little damage.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, this electricity is gonna piss me off later for sure.
Jesus Christ.
This is kind of a dangerous place for someone like me.
Whoa, good thing I'm immune to all that.
These enemies are very annoying to deal with.
Oh, I should just be using my chainsaw on them actually.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not immune to melee.
Don't be a dumbass now.
Let's grab some blood.
So it's good to see that even though they explode, we still get some blood out of it.
Which is all I wanted to know.
The run is still safe.
And I do have teleport.
Let's not forget about that.
What's up fools?
Man, I do get this PTSD reaction though when I see the electricity.
It's just inherent, you know?
Hard to shake off the fear of the electricity.
They just take damage.
No, it just says 75 sometimes.
It's a little bit weird.
Okay, come closer.
Come to me.
Come on now.
Oh, this is bullshit.
That's not water.
I'm taking some... I'm gonna take some damage here.
I can't avoid it.
Uh, blood, blood, blood, blood, blood, blood, blood.
There we go.
Let's get up here.
Let's just calm down for a second.
I'm definitely not feeling this one right now.
It's a little underpowered.
Got him.
Interestingly, they don't explode immediately.
It takes like a second after they die before they explode.
Oh, not this guy again.
He's difficult.
It's a duel.
He's stunned.
The electricity got him.
I'm like 100% sure that I can make a better one with what I have right now, but I just don't see it yet.
Right now, the solution to me, to my problems is one of the Admana spells.
That would be impeccable.
Or finding a wand where the mana charge speed is really high.
That's like the two big ones that can improve my situation right now.
Oh, not this guy again.
I kind of want to lure him to exactly so they get stunned.
Get him on the medal.
Did I get everyone?
Seems like it.
Losing a bit of HP here.
And it does feel like I'm losing blood here, given the explosion situation.
Enemies are exploding and they're not releasing as much blood, I think.
So I may have made a mistake picking that perk.
Come here, guys.
Asshole.
Getting so much money here.
Worm pheromone.
I mean, you can fire me all you want.
I'm immune, baby.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, this is the easy one.
133 HP.
Okay, so the electricity will blow up those things.
Probably that one, too.
Let's just play that safe.
Well, as safe as you can play it, I guess.
That thing probably also blows up from electricity.
Yeah, look, it's catching fire.
Just get rid of it.
Oh, no.
Do I really want to bother with him?
Probably not.
Let's see.
I'm just going to avoid him.
Go down this way.
It's this.
Ouch.
Actually, I would like some water, please.
I'm kind of stuck here.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
I think there is a bit of unstable in here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Got to get rid of that.
There we go.
Clean water the way I like it.
Very nice.
I'd like some more water, please.
Wait, what's going on there?
Oh, this thing.
I think it broke.
I really need to fight blood.
Yeah, look, the blood is gone.
I actually fucked myself a little bit taking that perk.
A friendo, but I don't have any pheromone.
So a little bit useless, I guess.
Damn.
So many froggies.
Oh, here we go.
Jesus Christ.
They keep coming.
Actually, I'm kind of in the trouble here.
I'm very low.
Shit.
What the fuck do I do?
I'm going to go back and take the health.
I'm going to play this safe.
I can't believe I actually destroyed my whole ability to heal.
Ah, that's terrible.
There's a bit of blood here.
Nah, I'm going to pick this.
I'm going to take this now.
Digging we can do.
Slightly, at least.
Just a bit of that.
There it is.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, we play it safe.
And we get that extra HP as well, because we found two hearts.
So that's nice.
Okay, I'm going to go left now.
Sometimes there's a huge pool of blood in here, you know?
I'll try and look for that and then try not to destroy it so I can utilize it later.
That's the current plan.
Look, he's bleeding, but it's all sort of mostly gone.
Ah, there's a bit of blood.
I'll pick that up.
Thanks.
You can still get some blood out of it.
Can I dig through here?
Yeah, actually.
Destroy that one and this one as well.
Actually, all of them.
I don't trust it.
Look at all that freezing vapor.
Whoa.
What do we got there?
Uh-oh.
Got a missile launcher.
Sir.
Oh, you're the one shooting.
I see him down there.
I'm gonna flank him.
There he is.
Oh, hello.
How am I gonna get to him?
Sick.
Come on.
Man, he's difficult to kill.
Oh, not this guy.
I always get hit by those things.
The good thing about the explosions is they kill each other with it.
This guy just can't die.
He can't hit me.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
Finally, he died, but there's one left.
Did they just kill each other?
From the explosion, I think.
Sir, this is a mess.
Pure chaos.
Oh, shit.
You bastard.
Ooh, he did a lot of that damage there.
Scary stuff.
Destroy that one.
Water this.
Kill him.
Beautiful stuff.
Let me just get some more water here.
Not that the water is that important anymore, actually.
Since I am immune to fire.
Ah, but it is important for toxic waste.
So, never mind.
It's still very much important.
Unstable crystal with trigger.
It's kind of an intriguing wand.
Zero castile.
I guess it's better than this.
It's not a lot better.
Holy HP.
The
main things I'm afraid of is acid, toxic waste.
And spiders.
Melee spiders.
And freezing vapor.
Actually, there's a bunch of things I'm afraid of.
And polymorph.
I'm afraid of most things.
Yeah.
Also, I'm going places I shouldn't go.
Back here, back here.
Retreat, plate safe.
Wait for them to come to you.
Do not engage into their home turf.
Much better.
One at a time, guys.
Form an orderly line.
Shit.
I teleported straight into that projectile there.
That was really bad.
Okay.
Ah, man.
We need to heal again soon.
Problem is, no blood.
No blood.
Corpses just explode.
I really expected those corpses to explode into a pool of blood, at least.
At least some blood, you know?
Hey, sir.
Got him.
Oh, that's scary.
Get out.
Oh, shit.
Oh, we're actually... Oh, are we dead?
Are we dead?
Water, water, water.
Oh, we got to get back.
Oh, we can't get back.
We have no way of digging.
Ah, this may be the end.
We completely eliminated our healing ability.
The vampirism is useless.
Huge mistake.
At least I learned my lesson there for next time.
Okay, come here.
Come up here.
Next.
Come on.
There we go.
Beautiful stuff.
Okay, my current plan is to go find a huge pool of blood in here somewhere.
And that is definitely in here somewhere.
We just got to find it.
Let's make this into water.
Very slowly.
I'm scared of that thing right there.
We got to take care of it.
Just let it pass.
Yes.
What do we have here?
We got a bit of blood.
I can probably eat that off the ground.
It's going to heal me a little bit.
Oh, wait, wait.
I took damage.
I ate something.
I shouldn't have.
Shit.
Wait, we got blood here.
That's a little bit.
Thank you.
Uh-oh.
There we go.
Got a little bit of healing.
Oh, yes, blood.
That's huge.
Make more blood.
69.
Nice.
Okay, there's enemies down there.
I've already been over here.
That thing is fucking terrifying.
I'm going to kill it.
We got some more blood here, but there's also toxic stuff.
I don't even think about it.
I took damage again.
I'm eating something I can't.
I think there's a bit of toxic waste that I'm accidentally consuming when I do that.
So that's that we got.
We got some blood here.
Mix it up.
This is huge.
Rotten meat.
Oh, carve it up.
My salvation.
Oh, that's huge.
That's huge.
Let's go.
Love rotten meat.
This
is full health.
Almost.
I will eat off the ground now.
I don't care.
There it is.
Full health.
Oh, never mind.
Let's go back.
Let's get rid of that.
And my nose is itchy.
Got him.
Any more corpses here?
Can I eat here?
Nice.
Okay, that was big.
I'm back in the game, baby.
Fungal Caverns.
Airfields extremely humid.
Righto.
Everyone dead?
Okay.
You know what?
I have an idea.
So enemies can either be killed by me or they can die from an accident.
Right?
If I throw a tablet at them and they die, I wonder if they blow up or not.
Hold on.
What does it say exactly?
Oh, it just says enemies explode upon death.
But I'm going to try it anyway.
If it said enemies killed by you explode upon death, maybe the story is different, you know?
But at least there was some chance there.
Oh, hello there.
How are you doing?
Whoa!
Calm down.
Everything's fine.
Just chillax.
Okay.
Man, what a fright.
Name a more scary thing in video games than that.
I dare you.
I double dare you.
I picked up more water than blood there.
That's fine.
I'll eat it off the ground.
That works.
Not actually sure what I'm doing in here.
Yes, I am.
I'm exploring.
We're trying to find once.
Not that interesting.
What is that thing there?
Why is this called blood?
It's not blood colored at all.
That's weird.
Oh, he died.
Okay.
That was a mage.
Scary stuff.
Oh, he has a wand.
He had a wand with an energy sphere.
Not that scary, actually.
Come to me.
Beautiful.
He's playing slow.
There's no reason to hurry up here.
We have all the time.
Wait for him to come over here.
He has the wand now.
Not that I'm scared of it.
It's kind of a shitty wand.
Yeah.
Exploding enemies is huge here.
When they're clumped up like that.
Really nice.
I see chests.
Ooh.
Damage plus.
Hey, short range homing.
I like it.
Some good stuff on there.
Very cool.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sorry.
Want to come over here?
He just wants to shoot some mines, it seems.
Nah, this guy is too scary.
I'm going to go around and flank him.
If I can.
That was smooth as hell.
Oh, he's summoning creatures.
That bastard.
This is kind of bad.
I need to somehow get around him and kill him.
There we go.
And he died to the electricity.
Lovely.
There's actually a wand there.
Which one is that?
Oh, that's the one I just left behind, of course.
Down.
That's molten metal.
I'm not immune to that, I don't think.
That's the same as lava, I guess.
Even though lava is technically molten rock.
Right?
So not quite the same.
Got him.
8,000 gold, by the way.
How do I have so much?
I don't even have a perk that gives me more gold or anything.
Jesus.
God damn.
Yeah, that's, that's, that's not good.
Go up here.
Take him on one at a time.
Come to me.
He just hit his friend with the goo.
And he got slowed down.
Next.
Okay, not bad.
That was well done.
Padding myself on the back here.
Jesus Christ, look at all the explosions.
Wait, why did all these people die?
The electricity, maybe.
Or maybe the acid.
There was some acid here.
I almost fell in the portal.
Close one.
I don't want to go in there yet.
Or do I?
I'll take some of this blood.
Aha.
Oh, I'm not scared of him.
I'm immune to electricity, baby.
You like them apples?
I'm just taking these shots to the face.
Melee though?
I can't take those to the face.
I can resist explosions, electricity, and fire.
But a fist to the face?
Nah, man.
That's my weakness.
My only weakness.
Got him.
And there's a lot of blood here.
Actually huge.
Nice.
More.
Is that all meat?
No, it's rusted steel.
Okay.
Well, that was nice.
Got a bit of healing out of that.
Uh, sir.
Talk to the hand is what he's saying.
Very good.
I'm playing really well.
Can I get to you?
Just hit you through the wall.
Hit the gold.
There you go.
Oh, that was bad.
That was straight in the face.
This guy... Oh, he died from it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He died from the electricity.
Amazing.
Very nice.
We love to see it.
Oh my god.
The whole gang is here.
Come join me, brothers.
Dude, imagine having the infinite breath perk.
Having someone follow you and just jump into the ocean.
They're gonna die.
In fact, everything in the ocean dies if I go in the ocean.
I'm gonna perform genocide of the fishes.
Killing all the fish.
Can I get in here?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I took a bit of damage there unnecessarily.
See, this right here is nightmare stuff.
What you're looking at.
But I'm okay.
Normally, that would be the end of me.
Within a couple of milliseconds.
I'm gonna be able to buy so much at the next holy mountain.
Aha!
A spell refresher just hiding there.
Come here.
These guys are tough.
I have a lot of trouble dealing with them.
Oh, whoa, the damage.
Oh no.
Fucking hell.
Oh my god.
This guy can't die.
Oh shit.
We gotta retreat.
Holy shit.
That guy is impervious.
Is it time to just leave?
I think we'll leave.
I can't get through.
We're out of here.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Fuck that.
Nope.
We leave that noise behind for sure.
Ooh, light shot.
Very nice if I find a black hole.
Ooh, a good old spark bolt with trigger.
Much better than this.
Oh yeah.
Lovely.
What do we have here?
Larpa bounce.
A projectile will launch a copy of itself when it bounces.
Yo.
Okay.
Water to poison?
No.
How about the other way?
Can I not have the... There's a wand down there.
What the hell?
Excuse me.
What?
Oh, you're kidding me.
Even more immunity.
Oh, that's interesting actually.
So wait, I bleed flammable oil, but I'm immune to fire.
But if I take this, I bleed flammable gas instead of blood.
I am super curious how this interacts with this perk.
What the hell?
But I think I gotta take the melee immunity.
We gotta take the immunities.
It's just too good.
How can you not take it?
Okay, we definitely need this wand in our lives.
Get rid of these guys.
We don't need them anymore.
They suck.
We don't need a nuke orbit.
That's a bit too violent, even for me.
Throw this away.
I would like to purchase, please, this wand.
Also, are any of these wands any good stat-wise?
Yes, but it's shuffle.
Shit.
This wand?
No.
Whoa!
Okay, that's a crazy good wand.
It does have two spells per cast though, but I think that's okay.
Yo, hello.
Look at that.
A thousand mana charge.
Dude, we can make some damage.
Throw this shit away.
Don't want it.
I need this bad boy right here.
It does have a lot of recharge time though, but we do have a spell called reduce recharge time.
So that's almost too good, right?
And put it here.
All of these.
Maybe you want to keep the orbiting arc.
It's intriguing.
Okay.
First off, where did I put the... Wait a minute.
Where did I put the spark bolt with trigger?
Am I blind?
It's not up here.
It's not on this wand.
Wait, where the hell did I put that?
I'm so confused.
Oh no, I never bought it.
I'm an idiot.
Now get rid of this.
Yoink.
Can't believe I just did that.
That was embarrassing.
Put this here.
Throw this shit away.
And then... Oh, we're gonna be making some good stuff here.
Let's just see how this works for now.
It's two spells per cast, but let's just see.
Okay, so it's kind of similar, I guess.
Now we put this in front.
Ready for this one?
Watch.
Oh, we still run out of mana.
Unless we... Nah, it's too fast.
It's too much mana cost.
Get rid of that maybe.
Oh man, it looks sexy though.
It looks really sexy.
Let me also see here.
So it's shooting this one.
That's the one that's costing all the mana, basically.
These are just one mana each.
It's not a lot.
I really expected this mana charge speed to be enough.
Let me get rid of one of these maybe.
Maybe one more.
I like that!
It's a little sweet spot, I guess.
You could definitely make it faster, but maybe not make it too fast.
Let me put this in here.
Does that help?
Is there a difference?
Actually, we're limited by recharge right now, right?
Yeah, that one also reduces recharge time.
In fact, maybe we don't need the reduce recharge if we have enough chainsaws here.
That's just for argument's sake.
Say we put a sparkle with trigger.
We put a quadruple.
We load it up with chainsaws.
Okay, it's not that fast.
What if we do this?
Oh, let me also think here.
Two spells per cast.
So this is the first spell, which contains this whole thing.
So this is just one spell really.
Now comes the second spell, which is that one, which is gonna look for this one.
No, no, no, apparently not.
Oh, we need to put one extra spell in here.
I think like that.
Can I?
Okay, nevermind.
No.
No, god damn it.
Aha!
Why is that so inaccurate though?
Oh, because it adds spread.
Is that the only reason?
That's six degrees of spread?
I guess so.
I mean, it's not too bad.
I can live with that.
And if we put an extra... what if we do this?
Oh, that's fast.
Yeah, so the reason we ran out of mana before is actually not too much the spark bolt.
It is the reduced recharge time.
That's the big one.
So if we can utilize these instead, we're golden.
Now we just gotta make it better.
So this is five mana drain, but let's see.
Okay, we're still at full mana.
That's... oh, we have made a much better one now.
Actually wild.
Now this one costs two mana.
We do this recharge time by 0.25, which is a little bit more than a chainsaw.
If I remove this, it's a little bit slower.
Let me just add an extra one just to test.
Honestly, most of my wand building is experimental and not much theory, because I think I've given up on trying to understand how the chainsaw works, because it definitely does more than it says.
It also says it has some magical properties...
you know, so a little bit mysterious.
But just playing around with it, you can get a feel for what it does, you know, and it's enough usually to get something going.
And this is gonna add lots of damage to all my chainsaws.
I'm happy with that.
Now, can we make it even better?
Even better.
What else do we have here?
Do we have anything here we would like?
Short-range homing is very expensive.
I feel like this is interesting.
Freezing gaze is awesome if you have infinite spells.
Makes the projectile move considerably faster, but deal less damage.
And that is a lot of less damage.
It's minus 25.
Damn.
But it does add a lot of projectile speed.
I wonder if we can use this light shot on a... whatchamacallit... dummy spell.
Hold on.
If I... I have an idea.
If I take this here, because I want some of this anyway.
Well, I want this one really.
If I can apply the light shot only to the spark bolt with triggers, so the three damage this one does, and not to all of these.
I wonder if that works that way.
Like, look at that.
The speed is so high now that the spread is negligible.
It's so fast.
According to the damage numbers here, it doesn't seem to be affecting too much.
Maybe a little bit.
It's hard to say.
Almost nothing, I would say.
Just doing anything.
I don't think so.
Nope, that's the same.
Here's the thing, though.
This costs two mana.
This is free.
Oh, wait a minute.
We can maybe add more stuff here.
Let's say we add a triple, and inside of that triple, we have a quadruple.
So this is just the first.
Okay.
And then we can add a bunch more crap.
What should I add?
What kind of crap do we want to add?
I would like to add a bunch of varied things.
That's too much mana for sure.
Adding light would not be a bad idea, I guess.
Just to get a little bit of vision.
Oh, that makes it really slow.
Oh, wait a minute.
Now it's a little bit slower.
The triple spell does not work exactly how I think, because this is two spells per cast, so it's a little bit finicky.
I guess...
Yeah, it's a little bit weird.
You know what?
I'm happy with this.
This is a huge upgrade.
Let's not look a gift horse in the mouth.
Also, this is four spells.
I only have three in here, so we need to add one more.
Unless that is what's happening.
Oh, wait a minute.
Are we double dipping on two chainsaws?
Because it spells per cast, too?
Is it a double double dibidoo?
Is it a quadruple dibidoo?
One, two, three, four, five chainsaws at the end.
Look, and then...
It's hard to time... There, two.
So this is the first spell being cast.
The second spell is this one, which contains all of this, but it's not done, because this one casts four spells, and this is one, two, three.
So it looks for one more, but that one more is gonna be two, because it's two spells per cast.
The quadruple dibidoo!
Awesome!
That's my wand.
I love it.
I love my wand.
Now we have some light as well.
We're not gonna run out of mana.
That's awesome.
I love it.
This wand, do I want it at all?
Not really.
I think these two wands can be wands that I replace.
Also, nullshot increases our projectile's duration.
Let me get rid of this static.
It's annoying to listen to.
There we go.
Uh, now I can think.
Increases our projectile's duration dramatically, but removes all damage and explosion from it.
That is interesting.
I don't think there's anything to use that on right now, but sure.
I'll keep this one, I think.
Oh, this one actually reduces spread.
But it still casts them in a trifurcated pattern, which is not ideal.
Yeah.
Honestly, might even just get rid of the wands completely.
It is a terrible wand, right?
It's actually okay.
Let me keep that one for now.
I'll replace it later.
In fact, it's better than this.
Yeah, just put my teleport on that for now.
That's even better.
Awesome.
It's not shuffled either, so...
Lovely stuff.
I think we have everything we need here.
It's time to move on.
Just double check.
Anything else we need to buy?
Don't think so.
I'm okay.
At least for now.
We still need a proper way to dig.
Haven't found that yet.
Ooh, that's lava.
Let's see the damage.
Oh!
What?
Oh, did I kill someone who teleported me?
Or did I accidentally shoot my teleport wand?
It's one of the two.
I don't know which one.
I definitely did something I shouldn't have.
Dude, my wand is slapping!
It's slap... it's so good now.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it feels good too.
It sounds good.
It feels good.
It tastes good.
Let's not get overeager.
Don't get overexcited.
That's when you die.
Don't be a dummy.
Ouch.
That hurt, man.
Let's grab some blood here.
I did forget to bring a chainsaw wand, but this one will chainsaw, so it's fine.
Yeah, look at that.
Totally works.
Blood me up.
Nice.
Very good.
I need to find a black hole or some kind of digging down here.
That's my immediate mission.
Because I gotta find a way back up, right?
I'm actually soon at the point where I need to go back up.
I'm not intending to just win here, by the way.
I hope you all know that.
Oh, that's a neat wand.
I like the stats on it.
I'll take it.
Don't like the spells very much, but the wand is grade A stuff.
Suck, fool.
Oh, that guy still has some immunity to my shenanigans, it seems.
Oh, yeah.
He definitely doesn't care about me.
Holy shit.
Manacharge speed of 1350.
And a bunch of magic missiles.
Spread minus 16 as well, but 11 spells per cast.
But a recharge time that is astronomical, so...
No bueno.
Senor.
A
minute.
I think that one...
makes things cursed.
It curses the rock or something.
Bye-bye.
You know what's great about this?
You know what I think is happening here?
I shoot so fast with my wand now, that I actually chainsaw my enemies before they manage to explode.
Remember, they explode after a short time.
But now I'm shooting so fast that I actually chainsaw them before that even happens.
So that's amazing.
I'll take that in, Viseeblium.
Appreciate it.
Remind me the red one.
Oh, that one.
That's right.
Makes everything collapse.
Is this the Hamis container?
Oh, the green one is the curse.
Okay.
Curse rock.
Green one.
Green is cursed.
That guy's scary.
He's a polymorph guy.
I really love the light I put on it too.
Are you able to see where I'm shooting?
Actually super important.
What's down here?
Weakening curse melee.
Target hit by a projectile takes 25 extra melee.
So here's what I'm wondering.
Chainsaw.
It says damage slice, but that's melee.
That has to be melee.
So if I put that in front, this thing is gonna fucking slap.
25 extra damage?
That's significant.
Personal lightning caster.
There's all kinds of goodies on this one.
Concentrated light bounce.
I don't even know what that is.
The wand is also dope.
This is sick wand.
Ah, recharge time kind of high.
I'll take it though.
I see potential.
God, I love how I changed the wand.
It's so good now.
I
love this effect.
Super neat.
Look, he's scared of me here.
Ooh, I almost died.
What the heck?
Why?
Oh, I guess the projectile he's returning.
Ooh, that was scary.
I gotta be really careful with those things.
I'll be taking some more blood, thanks.
Awesome.
Cool.
And I'm immune to that.
So I've been here already, but I can eat some blood.
And yes, I said eat.
Nothing like chewing on blood.
Mmm, that metallic taste.
Actually, I hate that taste.
I know some people love it.
It's weird.
Ah, to each their own, I guess.
But it doesn't make you kind of a vampire, no?
Which can be cool.
I mean...
Ah, Ukuskivi.
I'm not afraid of Ukuskivi.
Ukuskivi's my friend now.
I have become one with the Ukuskivi.
Don't you fuck in there.
One of the scariest enemies in the game right there.
He doesn't look like much, but oh boy.
He's a lot, okay?
Give
me blood over here.
Always have a full blood bottle.
That's what I was taught in school.
Whoops, what did I just do?
Oh, I shot this one without thinking.
That could have been disastrous depending on what was in there.
Uh-oh.
Don't even think about it.
Kill him!
Oi!
Can you stop shooting arrows at me, please?
Just a bit more.
I wouldn't mind getting a perk all seeing eye.
Because, unironically, it will save me in a lot of situations because I can see the polymorph coming.
What I'm most scared of here is the darkness.
Just getting hit by a polymorph off-screen or something from someone I didn't notice?
God damn, that's...
That's very sketchy, isn't it?
You can tell I've been scarred.
Polymorph cuts deep.
It's something I'll carry with me for the rest of my life.
You know that meme or gif of the dog who has like war visions next to the donuts or whatever it is?
Hahaha.
That's me when it comes to polymorph.
Gotta drink a bit more here.
Whoopsie daisy.
Uh, freezing vapor?
Where?
Where'd that come from?
What's in here?
Thank you.
Jesus.
There's a lot!
Look at all that gold!
One would think that I have the perk that gives more gold, but I don't.
These things just drop a lot of gold.
I guess it's also been a while since I was down here.
I forgot how lucrative this area is.
Stop.
I lost a lot of health.
Gotta find some blood.
Oh wait, I should be immune to that.
That should count as melee, no?
Arrows?
I did say close range.
I'm not quite sure.
I'm gonna drink from the floor.
The sat remains.
That blood?
It is.
Oh yeah.
Very gutsy blood.
You can tell there's hair in there, fingernails, organs.
It's just nasty stuff.
So could I actually go this way?
I guess so.
Look at that.
More blood.
I'll take that.
Collect some water first.
Told the bottle properly.
There we go.
And now blood.
Wait, I've already been here.
That was a bit risky.
I shouldn't have gone in like that.
Hey, sweet.
I'm okay.
Come on, something good.
Decent wand, actually.
A lot of capacity too.
That is a sick wand.
Maybe I like that more than this.
Yeah.
I'll take it, thanks.
Give me blood.
Oh, I don't want goop.
Uh, what's happening there?
Did someone get polymorphed?
I heard the sound effect.
Acceleration, okay.
But someone did get polymorphed.
My ears do not deceive me.
Man, look at all that gold.
Oh, yeah.
There's nothing like having a wand with a speed that just hits right, you know?
Like this speed right here is just perfect.
There's no audio issues with it, it's just smooth machine gun sound.
So good.
Look at
that gold.
13k gold.
Actually, not even that much, considering the prices of things later on.
I have seen things you people wouldn't believe.
Prices in the range of 25 000...
gold.
Sea beams, glittering in the dark near the tenhauser gate.
I guess I'll go down.
Oh, that was a scary situation.
I almost got hit.
Did you guys fucking see that?
God damn.
I saw the color of the projectile and I just had a crazy reaction.
My palms were sweaty.
And there's definitely something to be said about...
But I'm not gonna utter those words here.
Hey.
What do we have down here?
Oh, the laboratory.
Oh.
Hold on a second.
Did I mark this?
There's this weird little... I think I've seen this multiple times, too.
Whoops, didn't mean to do that.
Uh, standard.
Delete that.
And...
And I'm gonna take this one.
I'm gonna draw a little bit of an outcropping here.
I wonder why it says the laboratory right there.
The laboratory.
Maybe I entered the region over here that's called laboratory or something?
A laboratory.
Nice.
Okay.
Oh, not this guy.
Wait, he's different somehow.
Sir, why are you different?
It's so satisfying to see them blow up, actually.
The sound it makes is super satisfying.
Something about it.
Uh, what is that?
That's acceleration, I think.
Oh, let me get rid of you.
There we go.
You bastard.
Uh, I wonder if electricity can trigger those crystals.
I doubt it.
Okay.
Man, where's the end here?
Oh, but wait a minute.
Wasn't there something on the left?
That I could do here?
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, wait, I'm not here.
I'm here.
Whoops.
Hold on.
Mistakes were made.
Back.
I am here.
I was uh, I was about to say I want to go here now.
Because that is the way to go back up.
Okay.
Good, so this is actually the last.
Then there's a wizard stand on the right.
Yeah, we gotta go here and do this.
Because I don't have any digging.
That's the only way up.
The only way up is to go down.
Or in this case, left.
To the tower.
The tower.
With all the different layers of danger.
Very cool.
Up and left.
There is a chance I may not get here.
Because if it's blocked off and I can't dig.
Let's cross that bridge when we get to it.
Let's go.
Ah, that thing's about to explode.
Actually, hold on.
Uh, whoops.
I just touched the teleportation.
Oh, that's lava.
Oh, wait a minute.
I was just about to say actually, should I probably not go down to the next level and get a perk before I go up?
But the thing is, I can't go back up then.
I need some kind of way to dig.
Just a little bit.
I need to be able to dig through just a little bit.
Of brickwork.
Maybe I'll find something here.
To do that.
I really want to grab that perk before I go up.
You know, it feels like a ways not to take it.
It's a whole perk, man.
Could change everything.
Oh, hello.
Stop that.
Did I see a guy?
I saw a guy.
Oh, he's not the scary one though.
He's kind of scary, but he's not that scary.
You know, I'll take a bit of blood.
For the road.
Aha!
You bastard.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Actually, hold on.
That guy's not that scary.
If I don't do anything to him, he's not gonna hurt me.
Remember?
He's actually okay.
Look.
We're totally chilling.
No need to go nuts here.
So, at least he doesn't return the projectiles like the other guy.
He just starts to lead fire, it seems.
I'm okay with that.
Oh, did he just get blown up?
Amazing.
Hello.
Who else wants some?
It's weird.
I'm getting accustomed to the increased levitation speed.
I never thought that would happen, but it has happened.
I'm used to it.
Gonna be so weird going back now.
Oh, what's that?
Worm pheromone?
No.
That does hurt me.
Green is cursed.
Ah, a wand.
Not that great.
I mean, stats are actually decent, but I don't want any of this.
Don't want the eggs.
Even though there is no use for eggs, actually.
I kind of want to find just a couple more hearts, if I can.
Or, of course, black holes.
Black hole would be amazing right now.
Or even like a healing spell.
I mean, I still have vampirism, but the healing spell is for late game, you know?
It needs something more substantial than that.
Especially if I start to approach...
I don't know.
500 HP, you know?
Or even like a million.
That's a lot.
I keep taking little bits of chip damage here.
It's annoying.
What's up, fools?
Again, I lost so much there.
That crystal is no joke.
Really gotta watch out for that one.
Yeah, go up here.
What do we got?
Bastard.
Oh no, dead end.
I want to destroy that.
I'm coming.
Oh, it's so painful without digging.
Aha!
Very nice.
Oh, he has a wand!
No, wait, he doesn't.
Never mind.
It looked like he did.
Whoa!
Okay.
I'm okay.
I don't know why.
I just processed.
I'm gonna get stunned and I'm gonna get fall into the lava.
But I'm stunning me when I forgot that.
God damn.
That was scary.
That would be the killer combo.
It wasn't for my current perks.
Drink that.
Very good.
Now, how do I get up and left?
That's like the question here.
I may actually be locked off.
But I'm definitely not giving up until I've exhausted every option.
Okay, so I'm all the way up here.
The chainsaw does dig through some things.
It does not dig through that.
But maybe actually then Zrock.
So if I can find a little spot of dense rock, we could be in business.
Oh, not with this guy around though.
That's annoying.
Shit.
Nothing there.
Maybe further down and then up.
Here?
Maybe?
That does dig it, but...
I'm not sure it's gonna be enough.
Now, that's a bad idea.
Let's go here and see what's down here.
Oh, that's scary stuff.
More blocks.
Get out of here.
I'm gonna drink from the floor.
Like a nasty wizard.
What?
What was that sound just now?
I got scared.
Ah, that looks promising.
Maybe?
Ah, that's the guy with the returning projectiles.
He's scary.
Oh, we can take it easy.
Whoa!
I thought I moved out in time.
I didn't.
We gotta find more blood.
Okay.
I wonder if he dies to electricity.
Come here.
Standing this.
Actually, I'm scared because he may kill me if he gets hit by electricity.
Maybe he shoots things in return as well.
Come on.
Get touched by electricity.
Is he immune?
That bastard.
Hmm.
This is a bit risky what I'm doing here, but I need that blood.
Ah, I was too scared.
I don't want to do that anymore.
Oh, I see blood.
That is a lot of blood.
Oh, I'm rich in blood.
Oh, don't you shoot at me.
Crystals are scary.
Here we go.
Got him.
Kill up more.
Uh, what happened?
I just... wait, how did they die?
Did they actually die to electricity?
Because that's glorious, if that's the case.
They honestly just disappeared.
It could have been the explosions of the other ones I killed.
Actually, now that I think about it.
Probably they're very susceptible to explosive damage.
Because obviously chainsaws are not doing the trick here.
More of this, some of that.
Okay, let's go.
Sup fools.
I've come to claim your lives
and capture your wives.
Yep, that guy needs to die.
Scary stuff.
Just sip on that blood, will you?
God damn it.
It's all closed off here.
Maybe my map is incorrect.
Or maybe it changes every time.
It's a little bit weird.
This guy's gonna return, right?
Yeah, he is.
So the way to deal with him, I think, is to electricity.
Let's try it.
It was either that or explosions.
I wasn't quite sure.
Yeah.
Yeah, look, look, he takes damage.
He's definitely taking damage.
Come on now.
Yeah, touch.
Touch it.
Okay, whatever.
You can come with me, just...
Don't bother me, okay?
This is a one-man operation.
I work best alone.
Oh yeah, you want to get in here?
He's so annoying.
That's not happening.
Man, there's nowhere to go.
Maybe I was wrong.
Maybe it's not always that I can access that place.
Maybe it's a random thing that appears.
Aha!
What a find!
Another one!
Wow, look at this!
Right next to each other.
My luck is insane.
Getting some good HP here.
Actually, the whole electricity sound is starting to fade into the background for me.
It's become less of an issue the more... as time goes on, you know?
But I think as soon as it stops at some point, for whatever reason, maybe I die or whatever.
I'll start to notice how nice it is without it.
Right now, I'm okay.
No big deal.
Looks like I may be out of luck here.
Let's try going this way.
Okay, there's nothing here.
How about further... Can I go down here?
No, I cannot.
Damn, I don't even know where to go.
Fuck me.
That was my way out.
Uh-oh, I touched the Thalala.
Uh, I see you there lying in wait.
Oh, that could have been a poly... Oh no, he nullified me.
I've been nullified.
Let's just wait it out here.
Where'd you go?
I see you, little bastard.
Don't even think about it.
Oh, not this guy again.
Actually, let's lure him into the blood here.
Come on.
Yes.
Oh, oh no.
I'm confused.
Wait, why was I confused?
I'm not entirely sure what happened there.
I think that chest was a fake.
Or no, it contained money.
Another one.
It's been a while.
We can encourage electricity?
Ooh.
I mean, I already have some much good stuff.
I think I'll pass on this one for now.
Okay,
we reached the bottom here.
Haven't found a way.
Yes.
Another... Oh, nice.
So many hearts found down here though.
That's actually been crazy.
Been super lucky in that department.
Unstable polymorphine and a lot of it.
There's only one thing guys don't want and it's that.
And it's absolutely terrifying.
Oh, electrified, unstable polymorphine.
That's just not a good sight, is it?
Fuck off.
Yeah, nothing here.
I need me a black hole or something.
Unfortunately, there's been a critical lack of wants.
In this region.
So not much opportunity to find some new stuff.
Unless I have something on me right now that will dig.
Nothing there.
None of this I don't think will dig.
Why is everything shaking?
Concentrated mana.
You know what?
I'll take it.
Why not?
Seems pretty cool.
No!
The fire.
Jesus christ.
Jesus christus.
Man.
I can't handle that thing.
It's not good for my heart.
That shit scares me.
Need to be extra careful here now.
I can't fall into the trap of feeling safe, you know.
Did I check that?
I think I did.
It's already discovered.
So I checked that once.
Actually, I have an idea.
We could bring one of the crystals over there and explode it.
The ones that make everything go collapse.
Which is not green, not that one.
It's the red one.
We can probably find some red ones over here.
That's my plan.
The only question is...
Where exactly should I do it?
I think it's... according to my map, it's top left.
Let's see if we can make it happen.
Grab just a bit of blood here if it's okay with you guys.
Come on.
This is so sketchy.
That's it.
No more.
Too scared.
Here we go.
We got some red crystals.
Good thing they have low gravity, sort of.
That's gonna help me out here.
I'm just scared they suddenly break and things fall on my head.
Hey, nice.
Sick.
Look at this.
The sound they make when I kick them is not very...
Uh, what do you call it?
Oh!
Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry!
Jesus!
Okay, you get to die now.
I'm scared.
I'm tired of you.
We gotta hit him and then quickly get out of the way.
Like that.
There we go.
Smooth operator.
Where did the crystal go?
Oh, it broke or what?
Also, am I even going the right way?
I think up here.
Yeah, yeah.
This is the spot I would like to put a crystal.
Actually, wait a minute.
Can I dig through this?
What do I see?
I cannot.
It needs to be the dense rock, not the extremely dense.
Okay, hold on.
We haven't explored the whole region yet.
Maybe there's a wand with some good stuff on it.
Let's just keep exploring a little bit.
Maybe we'll find a black hole.
There's a chance.
Uh...
Damn.
Whoa!
Bastard.
You've already been over there.
How the hell did I even make it this far without any digging at all?
Kind of impressive.
Like I'm so harm strung by this limitation here.
Fuck, how do I bottom?
This way?
This is new, sort of.
No, not really.
I'm gonna eat from the floor.
This is so scuffed.
Here we go.
Imagine if that wand up there contains a black hole.
That would piss me off.
But I will never know.
Unless I find something to dig with.
Just a luminous drill, really.
I will gladly dig for 10 years.
If that's what it takes.
Just something, please.
Actually, I have an idea for something we can do.
We do have this place.
We could potentially try and go that way.
If anything.
And there's probably going to be wands in here, right?
Not the worst idea, I would say.
In a pinch.
Could work.
God damn it.
Stop hitting me.
That's a dead end.
Question is, can we even find that spot here?
Or are we also locked out of that?
Chest?
Oh my god.
There's something more over here, I think.
Down here?
That's lava.
Crazy thing is, I haven't even found a portal yet.
I guess I haven't really been looking either.
So this is that spot.
Where the hell?
Ah!
Here it is!
How do I do this in the best way?
I'm actually kind of scared of this.
Last time I won versus this guy, I had a black hole, I'm pretty sure.
And that seemed to be the key in the moment there.
I don't want to open a can of worms that I can't let back in, you know what I mean?
In any case, I think we would need to have an escape route planned out.
Down to a portal or something.
Just in case we need to get the fuck out of here.
Also, we need an egg.
Is this the portal?
Actually, I think it could be.
I could get lucky, go through the portal down here and hope for a digging spell in the holy mountain.
But that's a bit of a risk, isn't it?
I don't know if I'm willing to take that risk.
I think that's a bad idea.
Get out of my face.
Okay, there's definitely more to explore on the right.
Right and up.
Maybe.
So this is that spot.
If I go up from here, aha!
Some gold, I guess.
It's a bit of a tricky situation.
I don't want to go back up there.
I'm not actually sure what to do.
I actually have an idea.
But I need teleportation for that.
I wonder if I can somehow teleport back if I go through the portal, if I do it right.
You know?
Depends on the distance, of course.
Involved.
If I need to find a thin enough...
layer or whatever.
Want?
This could be big!
This could be the one.
I only just need to get up there.
Hey, it takes through here!
Wait, I've already seen this one, I think.
Oh my god!
That's incredible!
Incredible!
Wow, that's exactly what I needed!
That is unreal!
Damn!
I guess I'll replace this one.
And look at this with Nullshot as well!
Can it be any better?
Holy crap!
Okay, so...
Uh, let's actually find some blood.
As well, just so we can heal up a little bit.
May as well go a path we haven't taken here yet.
Man, that's a lot of sand!
Holy cannoli!
Wait, what?
Good amount of blood too!
I like it!
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink!
Oh yeah!
Lovely!
Oh, wait a minute!
That was an egg!
Maybe that would have worked!
Not that I want to go that way anyway now.
Never mind.
Everything's fine.
The only thing I don't like about my current black hole one is that it shoots two at a time.
Yeah.
A little bit iffy.
Man,
what is all this?
This whole area?
I haven't explored yet.
I thought I had explored the whole western side.
Guess I was wrong.
Holy blood!
Oh, okay, that's kind of scary with the lava below as well.
This looks crazy!
And get more blood.
Kind of want to fill up two bottles.
I don't need that much concentrated mana.
Or do I?
Nah, I'm gonna get rid of it.
Then again, no, I'm not.
I think I like it.
No, I don't need it for anything!
Be reasonable.
Piss it down here.
Come on.
I'm going full blood.
The rumbling of the lava is crazy nice sound.
I just love the way it sounds.
Like a nice hot soup that you want to consume on a cold winter day.
Is that a new wand?
Eggs!
Forgot about that one.
I found that one before.
I remember now.
Okay, I'm going...
So, I have a couple choices here.
I can dig down.
I can go through the portal, grab the perk and make my way back up again.
That's especially nice because I think I'm capable to murder Stewart quite handily.
So we should be all right on that front.
So yeah, seems like a solid idea.
I think I'll just do that.
And look at all this goddamn money I'm getting too.
Okay, here we are.
Should I go for it or what?
Let me think.
Let me just take another quick peek around here.
We're leaving!
Oh my god!
This game is giving me heart attacks!
What's that?
Vacuum, field, earthquake...
Uh, what's this one?
Warpcast?
Hold on, let me see the perks.
Maybe I don't like these.
I mean, extra perk is nice.
But it's kind of too late for that, you know?
But there are more perks to be found and I wonder if this will affect that.
I hope it will.
But I'm not sure, so I'm just gonna reroll.
More blood!
You can sense nearby items.
No, I'll reroll once more.
Ooh, invisibility!
I gotta take that.
That's amazing.
Thank you very much.
And now I will remove the double on that.
What happens if I double nullshot?
Think about that for a second.
Have you thought about it?
Okay.
Good, because I think it's crazy.
Bup!
How long does it last?
Ooh, that lasts a long time!
Holy shit!
Yo, that's way longer than I thought.
Stuart!
How you doing?
Wait.
I'm not doing anything to him.
Let me get in close.
Yeah!
Just getting close and that's it.
That's how you do it.
Lovely stuff.
Drink some blood.
Okay, okay, dude.
Okay.
Now, I'm gonna go top left.
Go this way.
I don't want to just use my black holes anywhere, because I have limited amounts.
I'm not there.
I need to go all the way to the top left.
Okay, so this is the middle.
I could try and see what that wand is now.
May not be the worst idea.
Yeah.
Aha!
Lightning bolts.
Nah, I'm okay.
But you also have a spell refresh up there, so if we run out of black holes, we can go back there.
Lovely stuff.
Right, this way.
By the way, hold on.
There's something I needed to experiment with in the tower.
And there's a little region here with something.
Remember?
Did I write that down?
Explore the... get all essences.
Did I not write something?
Hold on.
Oh, that's right.
Friendship or avarice?
Found this at the end of the tower.
Could mean pheromone or gold.
Ah, I don't have any of that on me.
Dang it.
Well, this is just what I wrote last time.
It could be wrong.
I don't know.
But it's the only clue I have right now.
To that little puzzle there.
Friendship or avarice?
Avarice is like excessive greed, right?
Uh,
are you gonna... okay, you're fine.
Bye-bye.
I'm just gonna fill up my, uh, blood bottle here.
My double blood bottle.
Also, hello.
Look at this.
Invisibilium is useless.
So I'm just gonna have... I'm gonna have three blood bottles.
People may think that's too much, but I will disagree.
You cannot have too much blood.
Oh, yeah, pee good.
Fill the last one up.
What is this?
Is it frozen blood, or what is happening there?
Let me grab a bit more.
There we go.
Look at that.
Three full blood potions.
And I honestly don't even need the water.
Actually, I do.
It is nice to turn toxic into... Oh my god, I just took damage again.
Like a dumbass.
Let me just grab a bit more then.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Come on.
No, I can't even grab it.
Okay, that's fine.
We're fine.
So the way is not...
here.
It's... Man, I forgot how I got up there.
Actually, I need to take a piss real bad.
I'm gonna find this spot, and then I'm gonna take a quick piss.
And I need to take a break anyway.
I need to hydrate and walk around.
Oh, here we are.
I made it!
Okay, I'm gonna take a quick break.
Uh, and I'll be back in like three minutes or something.
I'll see you then.
Bye-bye.
Actually, I'm gonna put it on...
here, so we get some music.
I'll see you in a bit.
All right, we're back.
I have upgraded my coke situation here.
There's now.
You hear it?
Ice cubes!
Oh, yeah, baby.
What an adventure, huh?
Back into it!
So, uh, let me just quickly check the map again.
Where exactly is this thing supposed to be?
So I just have to go left.
Why is it locked off?
It's... Unless it's not even here.
I mean, that could be the situation, I guess.
Okay, I'm just gonna go left.
Uh, how many black holes do we have?
We have...
seven.
And we have more, because we have a recharge thing.
Let me just go that way.
Look how long that lasts.
Wait a minute, didn't I also find something with speed?
I... Or maybe I didn't.
Oh, I did light shot!
Oh, but I can't change my wants.
Of course.
Oh!
I'm approaching something.
Hey!
I made it!
Oh, that was beautiful!
But wait, my map is wrong!
This doesn't look right.
Uh, I guess it's further down?
Because it goes down here.
Wait a minute.
Yeah?
Weird!
All right, well, whatever.
Wait, how does this work again?
I just...
I'm gonna make a hole.
Come
on, drain.
Look at that beauty.
Isn't that beautiful?
Get it.
Oh, here we are.
Okay, we're starting off hardcore here.
Let's not forget, we could be in a situation where we have a shortage of blood.
Let's be extra careful.
Wait, what the f- That's a shitty wand.
It's a wand befitting for the hemisphere.
Which is where I am right now.
Well, not really.
It's like a weird, nightmarish version of the hemisphere.
Yo, why am I not able to get through shields anymore?
I noticed that as well with the steward.
Something about my setup here is not ideal for that.
By the way, last time I was here, it was really bad.
I had lots of trouble getting through this place.
Oh!
I need to play safe.
Who was shooting?
You!
You little bat- Oh, this guy is buffing everyone.
You little asshole.
Can I even get through his shields?
I can't.
I gotta get in close.
This is not ideal.
It works.
Very sketchy though.
Uh, okay.
I just need to go up.
I'm gonna stick to one side like I did last time.
That worked pretty well.
Silver pouch.
You know what?
I'll take it.
If I am allowed.
Did I destroy it?
Oh no!
I had no idea I could destroy it.
Fuck!
I was gonna use it to pick up some potential gold!
Avarice!
Shit.
Those guys are extra dangerous when they die, by the way.
The big guy I killed here.
They polymorph.
That looks bad.
Well, I can cut my way through it.
Yeah, it's actually pretty- Okay.
Ooh, what's happening there?
Oh.
Oh!
I understand what's going on with that guy now.
I have that spell too.
He's using projectile thunderfield.
I met him once before and it was quite the horrible experience.
Man, these ones suck.
Uh...
You're gonna die, sir.
Nice.
Feels good being immune to electricity.
Actually feels incredible.
Careful, careful.
Oh shit.
What the hell is that?
Uh, oh, these guys are invisible.
We gotta find the crystal thingy.
Or just ignore them, honestly.
Oh no, he's immune now.
Yeah, this is not good.
We gotta go up, we gotta go up.
Get the hell out of dodge.
That's what I'll say.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, freezing is bad.
Ooh, it's looking bad.
This place is a nightmare.
I ran out of healing.
Gotta play it safe here.
I'm gonna be doing some digging here with my non-optimal digging wand.
Or sub-optimal is the word.
Okay, okay.
Damn.
I don't care about the gold.
I'm moving out.
Ah, not too close to the edge.
Oh, look at that!
Very cool.
Whoa.
Boom.
Oh, that's sketchy.
What's going on there?
Is it a sebum?
Also, hold on, I can just go invisible here.
I don't have to subscribe to the whole fighting situation.
I can, uh...
chillax.
Just need to get this water off of me.
I'm gonna go invisible and go through the entire level invisible.
Easy peasy.
Just gotta get this off of me.
Come on.
There we go.
I'm invisible.
It is kind of risky though.
Because sometimes I feel like enemies can see me still and I don't understand why.
This one looks good.
Okay, okay.
Let me go right.
There's water.
Water's bad.
Oh, I got stained.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, we're in it again.
Gotta fight a little bit.
Let's make a little hidey hole.
What's that?
Concentrated mana.
Gold, fungal, soil, grass.
And what is that?
Fox?
Yo, it's mostly gold.
We're gonna try it now.
Let's get that guy as I want.
Scary stuff.
This is shitty water.
Oh man.
Do I take damage here?
Am I too close to the wall?
I think I'm okay.
Okay, I'm invisible.
Does he know where I am?
Fuck you.
That guy's scary.
You can't see me.
You cannot see me.
Oh, nice.
Still invisible?
You don't know anything about me.
What's with these chests?
Oh god.
I'm tempted to destroy the chests.
I gotta see what's in them.
Come back here.
Okay, never mind.
Chests suck.
Make me invisible.
Good.
Okay, we've made it to hell.
If not, if we weren't already there, you know.
I'm stained, I'm stained.
Just wait a bit for that to wear off.
Dude, I am maximum gaming right now.
I'm so focused.
Shit, that's a bit too close to the wall.
Oh, that actually stains me standing on that shit.
The hell slime.
Okay, just standing on it is enough.
Oh no!
I keep getting more and more...
slimed.
Okay, we gotta fight a little bit here.
Maybe I'll just go through here.
I see you up there.
You are not as scary to me, you are fine.
I'm getting low on health.
Get the stains off of me.
Wait, did we make it?
That's the roof.
Oh, it looks good.
It looks good.
Hold on.
Uh, make a hole here first.
Want of swiftness.
Always cast nuke.
Recharge time minus 38?
Jesus.
Want of multitudes.
Damn.
Holy crap.
I don't know about the nuke part.
Want of swiftness.
This one is very nice.
I do like the swiftness.
Look at the stats on this bad boy.
Holy crap.
That is good.
That is really good.
But what do I replace?
Probably this one.
Even though I really want to try the weakening curse.
Bummer.
That's okay.
I can live without it.
I want that wand.
Now.
Over here.
Oh, hello there.
Uh, actually no no no no no no.
Don't go down there.
Here it is.
Right?
No?
Yeah, here we go.
Here we go.
The only problem is I have no good way of digging.
I do have my wand here.
This is actually fine.
Just open it up.
So this one says...
friendship or avarice.
That's what this means.
I translated that last time.
And I'm gonna try and pour gold on it because avarice is related to greed, right?
I wonder how much I'll need if it is gold.
I mean worst case, if it doesn't work, I'll just get rich.
Yeah.
Oh!
Wait, it worked?
All right, was that always there?
Wait, I'm confused.
Uh...
I think this was here last time too, by the way.
So maybe it's something to do with air.
Hmm, I don't know.
Friendship or avarice?
I'm thinking pheromone.
Is the next thing.
Or even a pheromone, uh, npc.
Like a friend, friendo, friendo!
Friendship, maybe.
But I don't have any pheromone.
Let me actually just note that.
Uh, no, it was here.
Gold is not, uh, pheromone.
I mean it could be, hold on, back.
It could be gold.
Maybe more, you know?
I can't just exclude it like that, that's a mistake.
Maybe more gold.
Probably not, but we'll see.
All right, let's go.
Okay, awesome.
We made it!
Back to the surface, baby!
Yeah!
Now we gotta find some blood.
There should be plenty of that in the hemisphere, no?
I'm pretty sure we produced a lot of that down here.
Or maybe not.
Wait, is this the one where it was always...
Oh, there's pipes everywhere producing rainwater.
Oh!
We've got a little situation here with...
I think.
Was it whiskey?
The whiskey puzzle.
I'm gonna go to the cave.
And then I'm gonna go into the cave next to the cave.
So I can catch myself a little bit of something nice.
You know what I mean.
Actually, wait a minute.
I just realized...
I have no place to change my wants.
We're actually in deep shit.
No, no, that's not true.
The only place we have is all the way at the bottom.
Oh, that's such a distance though.
Oh, no, that's bad.
That's really bad.
Anyway, let's just focus on one thing at a time here.
Whoops.
One thing at a time.
Give me light.
Okay, okay, this is fine.
Oh wait, I can teleport.
There we go.
Oh, go up again, go up again, go up again.
Up, up, up!
It's actually kind of sketchy what I'm doing here.
Okay,
so now I'm here.
This is not the spot.
Whoops, someone's shooting at me.
I can go up here, go up, up, up, up.
Nice, nice, nice.
Probably down there, right?
Yep.
Got it.
Dig, baby, dig.
Made it.
500.
Oh, no!
Nullified.
I'm just gonna stand here.
You have not seen me.
Stealthiest man.
Ah!
Okay.
Man, that is a huge debuff.
And it lasts 10 seconds.
It's crazy.
Absolutely nuts.
Right, I gotta kill this guy first.
I don't want to wake that statue up.
Even though sometimes they're my bro, sometimes they're not.
Is that?
Ooh!
Oh, wait, it's pheromone.
I was hoping for the other one, the one that gives you double damage.
There's actually a lot of that here, usually.
In fact, I'll try and find that before I engage the boss.
More pheromone.
Sweet.
What's that?
Concentrated man.
Okay, we're fine.
That's scary, though.
We don't want none of that.
No, sir.
Is that pheromone?
Okay.
Ah, it feels so nice being back close to the surface again, you know?
There's a certain safety in that feeling.
Feels good.
Man, you're immune, you bastard.
I need more blood, actually.
This guy came flying so fast.
Someone is buffing the buffer.
No more.
Where are you?
I know you're here.
I didn't get him.
Oh, I'm nullified.
Shit.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't go that way.
Here we go.
I guess I can still kick when I'm nullified.
You bastard!
Fucking hell.
Don't you...
Goddamn, you're annoying.
Absolute trash of an NPC.
There we go.
Taken out.
There's some scary stuff below me.
We don't want that.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
He's online.
And there's a polymorphism.
I don't like it.
Make that.
Oh, that's scary!
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
We are not doing that.
I'm going from above.
At least that way things can't fall on me, right?
Okay, here we go.
I'm gonna dig through here.
See where I end up.
What's that?
Concentrate a mana?
Okay.
Need an escape path.
Okay, we're here!
Oh, I'm scared.
Focus, focus, focus, focus.
Wait for the shield to be down.
Let's see what he does.
He shoots.
I get out of the way.
Attack.
Dodge.
Ah, I was too slow there.
Too slow.
Oh, that hurt a lot, actually.
Too slow again.
Oh, god.
Damn it.
Come on, shield down, at least.
Thank you.
There we go.
Focus up, focus up.
Okay, I hit him again.
Shield is gone.
Ah, it's gone.
Oh, wait, wait.
It's actually gone until I attack, actually.
Okay, trench warfare.
Out of the way, out of the way.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, get out of the way.
Oh, that hurt, that hurt a lot, that hurt a lot.
Get the fuck out of here.
Come on.
Shield's gone.
Good.
I'm very low HP.
Shield is still up.
Dodge out of the way.
Shield is down.
Hit him.
Get the fuck away from him.
Shield is down.
Dodge.
Come on, come on.
One more shot, one more shot.
Come on.
Fucking got him.
I got him.
That's how you do it, baby.
Okay, that was a bit sketchy.
I lost a lot of health there.
Oh, man.
Let me get rid of some stuff here.
Which ones are good?
I forget which ones are which.
I don't like that one very much.
Copies the two following spells in the Wand when cast.
Cool.
Uh, that's scary, actually.
Just wait it out.
Uh, hello?
Wow, that took a while.
Copies every static projectile type spell in the Wand when cast.
I will grab the last one too, but let me do this first.
Oh,
no, I still see some bullshit down there.
Get rid of it.
Are we okay?
I think we're okay.
Quickly grab and get out.
Cast a copy of the last spell in your Wand.
Okay, that's amazing.
Fuck yeah, dude.
Very cool.
Wait, how did I heal?
Wait, what just happened?
How?
Oh, he must have dropped some health or something.
I didn't even notice.
What the hell?
That's news to me.
The heck?
Okay, hold on.
Let's just, uh, calm down for a bit.
What is the plan?
Now I have these amazing spells.
I think the plan is to just go straight down here again.
We need to, uh, we need to edit once.
That's really all there is to it.
Really need to fill out this.
I'm gonna fill this out after this dream for sure.
I know approximately how this layout is now.
I'm like here, I wouldn't say.
Or maybe there.
Hard to say, but approximately.
Yeah.
Now we have to go through all the portals.
All the way down.
That's fine with me.
Let's get the hell on with it.
And you know what the good thing is here?
Oh, there's the berserkium.
Uh, I'll take some of it.
You know, okay, so my, uh, here's the plan.
We're gonna go down there.
We're gonna make infinite black holes.
And the healing situation is a little bit more problematic.
So I guess we'll go to, uh, Wandmart, as people call it, and find some healing again.
We're practically in the same position as we were last time I had a good run going, which is, you know, gotta find that healing.
And then with that healing, I'm gonna go east.
So we can find more perks.
Okay, the best way back is to just, uh, I guess I'm gonna make a black hole.
I don't care.
I don't have any left.
Oh, damn, okay.
Nah, I'm good.
Uh, okay, it's fine.
Shit, I can't see.
I can't see.
There we go.
Good stuff, good stuff.
That's one.
Uh, let me grab that.
Thanks.
Also, I can just take another look at all the stuff that I may have missed here that I would like to grab.
And maybe I will even...
So, when I take the portal, you arrive... here.
So, let me make it easier for myself in the future.
I'm gonna make a black hole straight down from here.
Oh, are you kidding me?
Bro.
There we go.
Man, that black hole went on for a while.
Man, this actually kills me.
Toxic is no joke, even right now.
There we go.
Wait, did I already make a hole here?
I guess I did.
Oh, and I have healing here too?
That's so nice.
Good to know.
What's that?
Nah.
I'm okay.
Just want to see what that one contains.
Really?
Critical on wet enemies?
Huh.
No!
Fuck!
Didn't mean to pick it up!
Ah well.
That's a bummer.
Is what it is.
That was a huge mistake.
Oh, okay, nice.
We got some blood here at least.
Uh, yeah.
Jesus Christ, look at all that blood.
Ah, let me take a quick look at the... stuff we got here.
What is that right there?
Oh, teleport bolt.
Eh, I'm good.
Eh, actually...
No, I'm good.
I'm okay.
Everyone's immune here?
What's happening?
The fuck?
There's a party going on!
And I was not invited!
I mean, I probably would have declined anyway, but you know, I have to get the invitation.
Interesting.
Always casts electric arc.
That's kind of dope for me.
But the one is not fantastic, you know.
I'm okay.
Hello!
Matilda made an appearance.
I don't think there's anything here I want.
Maybe oil.
Actually, wait a minute.
Oh, I can't... oh, but I can pick it up, of course.
I can still pick it up.
Give me that.
Let me make a hole here.
Nice.
I think just keeps going, huh?
Look how far it goes!
Let's see what we got here.
Basically, what I'm looking for here as well is also something like...
Oh, what's it called again?
The one that makes your spells hurt yourself.
In case I find deadly heal, you know.
I would like to be able to use it as well.
Okay, well, we almost made it.
Honestly, kind of fast.
I was expecting this journey to take a little longer.
Here.
Nice blood.
This way.
Here.
This place is kind of annoying to get through.
I guess I could use a black hole.
All right, here we are.
We can change once!
Amazing.
Can I just please go somewhere where the electricity is not gonna be annoying?
Here we go.
Okay, let's have a look-see.
Kind of want to put light shot on this one, honestly.
Not that it matters.
I'm gonna have infinite.
Cast a copy of the last spell.
I think I want that.
We only need one of these.
Fuck off.
There it is.
And that's it.
Infinite.
But wait a minute.
Why is it not getting null shot?
Aha!
Oh, okay.
Well, it works.
Why does it sound like someone is fapping off screen?
Do you hear that?
What the hell is going on?
Who's doing that?
Oh, was it this guy?
I think it was this guy flapping his wings.
It's just like...
I was so confused.
All right, go up here.
Now, this one is solid.
Done.
Next, what do I want to make infinite of?
Maybe this one.
No, wait, where is it?
That one.
Projectile Thunderfield.
It does cost 140 mana.
But it could be fun.
Orbiting Ark.
A projectile orbits the point of its origin?
That could be cool with Deadly Heal if I find it.
So what I'm thinking with oil, by the way, is...
If I can put that on fire every time, say with a burning modifier.
We can put everything on fire.
Wouldn't that be great?
But wait, how does this actually work?
Whoa, this one also reduces a bunch of castile and recharge time.
What the hell?
Where's the oil though?
Oh, there's a bit of oil.
Yeah, I think I'm okay.
We don't have any fire anyway.
I think...
I'm trying to... Okay, so here's the thing.
The problem is we can't change our wands, right?
So if we go to Wand Mart, we really need to be able to pick up some wands that we find.
I don't want to be... I don't want to have to come back here.
So I'm almost considering dropping teleport or even combining these two somehow.
Let me see what that would feel like.
Whoops, let's be careful where I shoot that actually.
And maybe one of them would be enough.
We don't need to make it that far.
I actually don't like it when it's too far.
I can always shoot more if I need it, right?
Uh, let's get rid of this one.
So wait, I'm thinking...
Like that?
Oh, I don't have enough mana?
Wait, how does that work?
There's 900 mana max.
That shouldn't be an issue.
No!
I hate myself.
I can't believe it.
Why is this not working?
So it should cast teleport bolt and then it should cast...
That one.
Uh, hmm.
Cast a copy of the last spell and you want.
What if I put this after?
What happened then?
Then it works, kind of.
But that's not what I want.
I don't want to do that.
That seems...
You know what?
Maybe I will drop the teleport for now.
It sounds crazy!
Teleport is really a lifesaver, but I don't want to have to come back here twice.
It is that bad.
You don't want to have to come back here twice.
I'm gonna drop these two ones.
I get... Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Also forgot.
I need to transfer all my stuff to this wand.
What the fuck am I doing?
Forgot about that part.
Can you stop electrifying shit?
Oh god, it's so annoying.
There we go.
Oh, but then I can't change.
Here we go.
Uh, put it down here.
Almost forgot about that part.
Would have been quite funny, wouldn't it?
Uh, whoops.
I feel like maybe I need some different damage here.
I only have damage slice.
Which seems to be a problem with some enemies.
If I go like that instead.
I mean, it does reduce my mana, but it's definitely enough.
It recharges quite fast.
I think this is cool.
You know, just have a bit of different damage in there.
And there's some explosive stuff as well.
It's kind of cool.
And it digs!
Which is awesome as well, actually.
I like it.
Um, so that's my damage wand.
Could even throw another one on there.
Is that okay?
One, two, three, four.
That is totally fine.
Nice, more damage.
Uh, okay.
Then we have this guy and then we replace two wands.
Yep, that seems good.
Honestly, this one is even better right now.
It has more charge speed, but...
This one is solid.
If we find an add mana, we're probably gonna find one.
All right, let's go.
Let's move.
Actually, wait a minute.
How much does this cost?
70.
No, that's not gonna work.
That's too much.
I'll keep it though.
All right, let's go.
No.
Right, no teleports.
Good thing I have the levitation boost, huh?
That's gonna help me out a lot, actually, when I ascend here.
Just to confirm that I have infinite.
Wait, hold up, hold up.
We got an issue.
It's not working.
Wait a minute.
There we go.
We are back on track.
Imagine I went too far.
I mean, I couldn't have gone too far, because I need the black.
Now I can just use black hole to go up.
Really super easy too.
In fact, since I'm here and I have a black hole, how about we have some fun with this dude?
Excuse you?
Wow, you're gonna be like that?
Hey, sir.
That is not okay.
Huh, he doesn't wake up.
All right.
I guess you do need an egg after all.
I thought I could maybe wake him up like that.
Actually, I don't want to go that way.
It's too much lava.
Also, I just had an idea.
Why don't I just go right?
And go up from there instead of going through all the regions?
Ah, you know what?
I have changed my mind.
I'm gonna go back and put a null shot on it.
I want it to last a little longer.
There's an issue here.
I don't know what the issue is.
What is the issue?
Oh, this one adds a bunch of castile and so does that.
We're actually castile limited on that one.
It's kind of annoying.
Let me see if I can fix that before I move on.
This is gonna annoy me for sure.
Hold up a second.
Reduce castile that one.
No, wait, that's recharge time.
Castile.
I guess that one reduces.
And that one reduces.
Let me just test here.
That's too long still.
Let's add some... I guess that one.
Okay, it's a little bit better, I think.
Actually, wait a minute.
Uh,
the null shot is not affecting it.
Huh.
Man, this is a real fucker.
Wait a minute.
Maybe I'll try this one instead.
Tau.
Copies the two following spells in the Wand when cast.
Let's try that one instead.
Let's put the null shot.
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, that's expensive mana-wise.
Let's put it on here instead.
The following two spells.
Wait, do I really have to do this?
Wait, what?
The black hole was invisible, I think, because of that one.
Okay, it's a little faster.
Actually, chainsaw does reduce.
No, that's recharge time.
Uh, I'm fine with this.
I think.
Copies a cast a copy of the last spell in you want.
That should work, no?
There it is.
Beautiful stuff.
Now I'm happy.
I'm thinking of putting the light shot on as well.
I don't know if I should.
No, probably not.
That makes this wand, you know?
Without that, this wand is not that good.
It's not very precise.
It's just kind of trash.
Put it here, please.
Yeah, that's the perfect speed, especially when I can't teleport anyway.
We're fine.
There we go.
I do feel naked without teleport, if that makes sense.
Shit, I need to water myself.
I keep wanting to try to teleport, but I can't.
Let me just go this way.
This whole world is going to look like Swiss cheese when I'm done with it.
And you know what?
I'm happy about that.
I do love me some cheese.
You don't... Wait, what?
Oh, no fucking way.
I'm here?
Huh, that's funny.
Wait a minute.
Let me see this wand.
Hey!
Ah, dude.
I wish I had Tinken with wands.
Fuck.
Wake up.
Wake up, wake up.
Got him.
Yes, baby.
I needed that.
Now when we find Deadly Heal, we are perfectly fine.
Oh, that's huge.
Okay, we're going back down.
Which sucks ass, but it is what it is.
I gotta go back down with all this.
Fuck.
You know what?
Make black holes, please.
What we need is a black hole highway, actually.
Just straight down, you know?
Okay, that works.
Oh, shit.
Scary stuff?
That's how fast things can turn, you know?
And I made it.
Keep that here.
This whole wand can go away.
I will put this on here, I think.
Yeah.
And then I don't need Nullshot.
That'll make it... That's too much.
That's actually too much.
Uh, get rid of this one.
This is more controlled.
Yeah, I like that more.
I like that a lot.
Okay.
And then we have a rock.
Definitely want that.
So let's put that there.
Get rid of that.
Now we have a rock.
We can have... We can make a rock wand if we want to.
That's super freaking awesome.
This wand can go away.
And we're back.
Let's go again.
And find some blood on the way up, too.
That's the plan.
That's actually so important.
If we find Deadly Heal, I am set.
Oh, yeah, the lightshot is totally making the difference here.
Oh, be careful.
That's the one problem with shooting black holes upwards, you know?
It's a bit risky.
But it's fun.
You never know what you're gonna get.
Yeah, that's scary.
Haha.
Son, you want some?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's way too risky.
Did you see all that polymorphine?
Yikes.
More polymorphine.
I've been polymorphing a lot, actually, in this run.
Uh, I'll just go here.
I know this one is safe.
Lovely.
And back we are.
Look at all this blood!
Oh, wait.
Uh, can I maybe make the blood over here, please?
Oh, yeah.
That's the stuff.
There we go.
I'm gonna fill up my main bottle as well.
Just a bit.
There we are.
Going straight up.
I need to be ready to emergency black hole either right or left in case something falls down on me.
Let's make it at an angle, actually.
A little bit of an angle.
Aha!
Whoa.
Okay, it's just water.
Hey, dude.
Oh, I know where to go.
I know where to go.
We're going this way.
Oh, and by the way, uh, we're gonna go get the, uh, music wand.
Because I have figured out what this means.
I'm like 99% sure.
That is indeed music.
You can play.
Those are notes.
I don't know if I told you this last time, but I went on YouTube to actually learn about musical notes.
And I learned about A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
Uh, wait, is it here?
Further up, I think.
I can hear it.
There it is.
Ah, so nice.
Look at that.
Cool.
Very good.
Even more health.
What is the best way?
I can probably make some kind of shortcut.
The overgrown camera.
Let's see here.
So I am here.
What if I...
So straight across from where this health was.
Let's try and be consistent.
So every time I'm here and I go straight across on the right, what if I black hole that way?
Let's see where I will end up.
And I'm gonna try and make it as horizontal as I possibly can here.
So this is where the health was.
Oh, okay.
We're fine.
Okay, here.
Right.
Oh, and I forgot to change the thing, because I could hear the music.
That's the fail save right there.
Man, I'm slow walking though.
Sure wish I had some acceleration.
It's kind of hard to make it horizontal.
Okay, so and I keep going horizontal from here.
Now we're in the desert.
The air feels hot.
Oh, oh, I'm invisible.
Oh, what's up guys?
How you doing?
Oh, okay.
Careful, careful.
Aim left, aim left.
Okay, it's gone, it's gone.
Scary stuff, scary stuff.
I'm deathly afraid.
Okay, we got some more dense rock.
Actually, this will make me walk faster.
If I recoil a little bit.
Sand cave, huh?
That makes sense.
Look, I think I should make the sand cave a little bit deeper than actually.
It's not quite correct.
More like so.
Let's just make it like that.
Very cool.
Switch back.
Keep going right.
Straight to Walmart.
Hit me with that dense rock fam.
We got poison man.
Nah, leave him.
Don't care.
Oh, let's spun these around.
Didn't trigger them.
Oh man, imagine if we can go to the east and find Tinker with Wands.
Holy shit, that would be insane.
I have hopes.
Okay, here we go.
We should be... yeah, we should be almost there.
We should be pretty much here now.
Put
this back, disable that.
There we go.
Very good.
Aha, and here are the Wands.
Amazing.
I'm just a little bit scared here.
Oh wait, I'm immune to melee.
Don't forget that.
Show me that wand up there.
Heavy shot.
Greatly increases the damage done by a projectile at the cost of its speed.
Oh, that's pretty good.
I think I'll take that for now.
That's a lot of extra damage.
This is considered a projectile, right?
Yeah, it is.
Okay, cool.
Heavy shot.
Hell yeah.
Okay, so let's do the systematic this time.
I'm gonna go at the very top all the way to the right, then we go one level lower and then... okay, we're already here.
What?
Never mind, that plan fell to ruin immediately.
All right, we're just gonna wing it like we always do.
We're just gonna go where the wind takes us and go where it feels right, you know?
It just needs to feel right.
Do you want to go grab the moon radar?
That should be here on the right side.
There's some health.
And would you look at that?
We freaking did it.
It does shoot it quite fast.
That's interesting.
But I'm not leaving until we find ad mana as well.
Or even...
Dude, the ultimate healing would be the circle healing.
But of course, that's the ultimate, you know?
That's the end goal.
Shit.
What do we got?
More healing.
And some other bullshit.
Very lucky with the healing here.
Got an Okuskivi in there?
Yeah, that did indeed contain an Okuskivi.
Yo, I heard you like magic bolts.
So we put a magic bolt inside your magic bolt.
Is that meme too old?
Am I getting too fucking old?
I know that was a funny meme some years ago, but maybe I'm too old.
Nothing there.
Show me those ones, fam.
Oh, that's the one I just checked out.
So we go down instead.
A
bunch of bombs.
Very cool.
I'm pretty much immune to most damage in here.
It's amazing.
Thunder charge.
Would love to put that on my wand if I have ad mana or something like it.
Or five ad manas even.
We can encourage melee again.
Maybe I will take it with me.
Heavy shot.
I've never really experimented with these weakening curses.
I think I'm going to try and experiment with it.
Fuck the heavy shot.
At least for now.
Maybe I'll change my mind later.
And we did that one.
Let's go left.
Oh, nice.
More health.
Another light shot.
I've gotten so many of them.
I see another wand.
Oh, something I've noticed.
I haven't had slowdowns in this game for a while.
Maybe he got patched.
I am running flawlessly right now.
Feels good, man.
Holy shit.
So many things, but not the one I want.
Although digging blast could be...
No, I don't need that.
I can dig.
I have infinite digging.
I have the best digging there is.
The best digging in the land.
More thunder charge.
What's that?
Always casts vertical barrier.
That seems like a bit of a death trap.
Freezing gaze could be cool here actually with the infinite spells we have.
Well, I gotta prioritize.
I have two spells that give me infinite spells.
I need one for black hole and I need one for heal, so we can't actually do that.
Which means we can't do the rock either.
No Dwayne Johnson this time.
Unless we of course find unlimited spells.
Is that gold?
Damn.
Why was there a mountain of gold?
Very unusual.
Oh, I just lost a lot of HP there.
I think I got hit by a bunch of Poland.
Shit.
Let me drink some of this.
Nothing interesting on that wand either.
Chaotic polymorphine.
Let me get the fuck away from that.
I checked that one already.
Nope.
No good, sir.
So many spells here.
That's my wand.
I left that there earlier.
There we go.
What's this?
Oh, I think I checked that one.
Unless there's just multiple thunder charges here.
Didn't that enemy look like he was in the wrong aspect ratio?
Kind of hard to explain, but he was like elongated.
Uh-oh, what's that?
Oh, I thought it was polymorphine.
Jesus Christ, look at all those spells.
Piercing shots, actually.
Harmful to the caster.
If I find deadly heal,
petrify turns a wounded enemy into stone.
Dude.
What?
Toxic mist always casts tentacle.
I'm kind of intrigued by this one.
Maybe I'll take that instead of the weakening curse.
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'll be grabbing that, thanks.
Boo, nothing interesting there.
Blood is kind of scarce down here.
So there's not going to be any healing.
Unless we find some liquid we can bathe in and hit ourselves with healing bolt.
In fact, how much did that heal us for?
Wait, nine?
Mine is nine?
That's not a lot.
Unless we can find a way to machine gun it.
That's actually kind of terrible.
Hey, I need something better.
Not what I need.
Did you just take that wand?
Don't you know all wands belong to me?
Chaos way.
What does Larpa even mean?
Isn't that something people do when they wear robes and stuff in the forest?
Let's go left.
I'll be taking this.
Thank you.
I'm actually starting to get a respectable amount of HP here.
Is that blood?
We got blood.
I'll be taking that, thanks.
Also, we could get high.
Did I ever get high?
In this run, I don't remember.
No, no, I didn't.
I would see it over here.
I did not get high yet, but it is a risk.
You do with another heart.
My god, nice.
You do throw the dice, right?
When you do that.
Oh, but look at all that weird fungus just waiting to be consumed and slurped.
I've been here already.
I've been here already as well.
Just keep going down.
Jesus.
Oh, that hurts.
You bastard.
That guy is difficult.
We got to be aware of them.
Man, what's with the hearts here?
So many.
So lucky.
You need teleports?
That enemy is scary.
He's the only one who can hurt me here.
It's the Poland.
And, of course, poison or acid.
We can encourage explosives.
Huh?
I don't know.
Nah, not yet.
This one, I'm very intrigued by.
The venomous curse.
Imbuse a projectile with a curse that makes the target hit by the projectile to waste away.
The way I read that is like, it's sort of a scaling thing.
You know, let's say the enemy has a billion HP.
It would still take like a percentage damage per second or something.
That's how I imagine that spell when I read it.
But I don't know.
Could be wrong.
Oh my god.
Oh, the Poland are fucking insane.
I'm gonna die to it.
Come on, man.
Give me my healing so I can go.
I need to get the hell out of here.
I'll take that.
Random damage.
No.
Yeah.
At mana!
That's huge.
Hmm.
Maybe I'll replace this.
Is that a crime?
Unless... Okay, so it's kind of close to the western edge.
At mana, close to the western edge.
Let's see what else I can find in here first.
Because whatever else I find in here will determine whether or not I will take that.
Let's remember, it is close to the edge here.
So just somewhere there.
Good to know.
What's that?
No.
Wait, what does that say?
Did it say blood to water?
No, blood to acid.
Yikes.
Oh, uh, the little spikes hurt as well, of course.
That's another thing to be afraid of.
Come on, show me some love.
What's that?
Nah.
Oh, thanks.
I'm getting lots of opportunities, though, to get some spells here.
I'm finding so many wands.
And more health.
Sometimes my shots go through the enemies.
I don't understand.
Okay, I guess I sort of explored this part.
Show me them wands.
Damn it.
Also a nothing burger.
Wow.
Weakening curse projectiles.
That seems pretty nice, doesn't it?
Just 25% more damage straight up.
If you're using projectiles, that's a significant increase.
Very good scaling, too.
If you have like a lot of damage, 25% is gonna be quite the extra.
Getting a little low on HP here.
If I get below 100, I think I may have to go back and heal.
Find one of the healing ones in one of the holy mountains.
Or find some blood, of course.
Hey, actually, we have some blood here.
Actually, these guys drop blood.
I can farm this area a little bit.
There's a bunch of humans here.
Humanoids.
That will produce blood for me.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink.
Wow.
That actually looked kind of cool.
Looked like a fighter squadron.
Flying information.
Bad asshole.
You know what?
Actually, the energy sphere that I'm using here, or the energy orb, is actually kind of messing with me and my blood collection.
It's not very ideal for that purpose, I've realized.
Because it blows up the blood, or the terrain, and then the blood goes away.
There we go.
Get some good blood going.
Wait, I can eat sand?
Dude, healing with blood right now is not ideal.
It's too much HP.
Oh, what the... That was a chaos die.
Nothing.
What's up, guys?
I've been here already.
Oh, nice.
More health.
There's so much of that here.
Wasn't this place a lot bigger?
Hold on.
Where is the moon radar?
Let's go and find that, actually.
Probably that will take me to more wands anyway.
Somewhere up to the right.
Ah, yeah, up to the right.
Even more health.
Jesus Christ.
This is insanely lucky.
More healing, but it's the wrong kind.
Uh-oh.
That's polymorphism.
Nope.
Also, a useless wand.
What's that?
Inviscibility.
I'm not afraid of that.
More health.
Come on.
Be good to me.
What's that?
Autoaim.
The description of that one is confusing to me when I think of...
homing.
No, thanks.
Is there more over here?
It is unexplored.
Any wand could be the wand, you know.
Just concentrate a mana.
We're fine.
Bomb cards.
That's a weird spell.
Someone is shooting a flitter.
What the hell is going on?
Wait, what's happening?
What?
Guiding powder.
It's guiding me.
Wait, what?
What the hell is this?
Can I eat it?
It's burning.
Uh, yeah.
Very confusing.
Oh, I'm confused now.
Yo, my whole screen is just shaking near that stuff.
I wonder if I had a pouch I could pick it up.
No, that's flammoxium, but...
guiding powder.
Doesn't it kind of look like flammoxium but on fire?
I wonder if that produces guiding powder.
Oh my god, my screen is shaking so much.
I gotta get out of here.
Whoa.
Give me that.
Critical on burning?
Could actually be kind of cool.
I imagine if you do this right, you can do so much damage.
You know?
But you would need the burning thing as well.
Get out of my sight.
I'm at 165.
It's a bit scary.
Give me the healing that I seek.
What did that contain?
Probably an ukuscivi or something.
Jesus Christ!
The pollen!
We're leaving.
We are leaving.
No more.
That's the straw that broke the camel's back.
Whatever you say.
I'll explore this one while I'm here.
Just show me what that is.
Nope.
That's scary.
Don't hit me.
Let me just see what I have.
Okay, okay, okay.
That's a bit risky going there.
I'm going here instead.
Also, I'm invisible.
Everything's fine.
Okay.
Left.
He managed to get one single hit on me there.
Two hits.
I could potentially find blood.
Yeah, exactly.
There's a bit of blood there, but not really available to be picked up.
Oh, more of it!
Just stay on their cover.
Oh, what's that?
What am I hearing?
Oh, we're here!
Hey!
Wait a minute.
Where am I?
Secrets of undeath have been unlocked to you.
Wait, hold on.
What?
Makes corpses of creatures killed by a projectile rise to your aid.
Oh, dude, I already got this one before, but because I had to reload an earlier world, remember?
Oh, man.
God damn it.
That's actually so sad, by the way, that I had to do that.
Wait,
I'm poisoned, but I'm okay.
We need to fucking leave.
I wish I had teleport.
This is just so risky.
I need to be invisible.
Fuck off.
Shit.
Jesus Christ.
Get this oil off of me.
God damn.
Okay, where are we now?
Here.
Okay.
Just stay invisible under the radar.
Just pass by unnoticed.
They have no idea.
Wait, I'm here.
I know where I am.
This is the huge rock fungus.
This is way too close.
I don't remember exactly where I have healing.
I think I have it in one of the holy mountains.
Otherwise, there is blood to be had somewhere, for sure.
Oh, I'm here now.
Okay.
Actually, this may be...
I think I healed in the very first holy mount.
I also picked a couple up by accident, of course, which was a huge mistake.
I'm just gonna fly under the radar here.
Oh,
I will actually check this.
You never know.
I could have been the one.
Tell me there's healing.
Shit, there's not.
The next one then.
And get this water off of me.
Is it just... is it flying through the air?
Is it walking?
I'm not quite sure.
Also, wait a minute.
Healing bolt, of course.
Hold on.
Oh, but the water is going to be so annoying.
Did that work?
Yeah.
Kind of a waste though, that I shoot three at the same time.
But it is what it is.
Shit, I missed it.
Oh, I could also chase it.
Look.
That's a... I'm not quite sure what's better.
Yeah, that's it.
That works beautifully.
A chaser.
This is so scuffed.
This is the worst way of feeling ever.
It's so slow.
Oh, man.
But right now, I'm just doing it for safety.
I just need some kind of health buffer here before I go further down.
This is just too dangerous to go down there with 30 HP, you know?
You gotta have at least a little bit.
Actually, maybe I can just stay in the water.
Wait, I'm out?
Oh, I'm out.
Okay.
But I could take this.
Not gonna though.
Actually, I am gonna.
Yeah, why not?
Gotta play this safe.
Shit, I think I missed that one.
Got it.
I'm trying to see if I can catch two of them at the same time.
Probably not.
Okay, that's a good start.
Let's go.
Now we're at least a little bit safe.
Let's find some blood.
Here we go.
Look at this.
And gold, too.
Actually, it's on because of the electricity.
Look.
Isn't that funny?
That's hilarious.
Too bad it's fucking destroying the gold.
I wonder if I just keep this on.
How long it will keep going.
Like, how far down is it gonna...
Oh, it actually goes quite far.
Wait, what?
Wait, what did I just pick up?
Why did it go ding?
Was it a chest that contained a wand or what?
Give me a bit more here.
I want to make my way all the way down again so I can...
My plan is to make some kind of machine gun wand out of the healing, at least, so I have something, you know?
Just gotta get the blood here.
Beautiful.
Man, this is gonna take a while.
This is just not worth it.
I mean, we're gonna heal up full once.
Actually, not all the way because I want to test the healing.
So this is it.
Yeah, just keep falling.
Oh, whoops.
And here we are.
Okay, so here's my plan.
I'm gonna try and utilize orbiting arc and machine gun the shit out of these.
And I'm gonna do it with, I guess, chainsaws and stuff.
And also, tau.
Or even, I'll use this one because it costs less for now.
Gamma.
Gamma, the last spell, orbiting arc is free.
Let's see how that even works.
Hey, not bad.
Wait.
Oh, that adds three damage.
That's funny.
Kind of annoying, but I still get healed by it.
Like, the net is still healed, you know?
Uh, god, I hate that I'm so slippery.
Can we please not stand here?
Okay.
Uh, what else can I do?
Increases projectiles duration dramatically, but removes all damage and explosion from it, eh?
Maybe not bad.
Also, this one sucks, of course, because of the long recharge time, so we gotta put it on something else.
Let's put it on this one.
Are they all?
Wait, just keep orbiting.
Oh, wait a minute.
Increases the projectiles duration dramatically, but removes all damage and explosion from it.
So, oh wait, does the damage minus nine actually count as damage?
So, it actually removes all the healing.
Uh, fuck me.
Wait a minute.
There's gotta be a way to do this.
Maybe bloodlust?
No, that's gonna be... even the net is not gonna be...
I can try piercing shot, actually.
That one will not give extra damage, but it will make it damage me.
No.
What about?
Okay, so null shot is bad.
Put this back.
What else do I have?
I guess I can just do it like this.
I mean, it's totally fine, I guess.
Like, if I can machine gun this, the net is still healed, you know?
Look.
Also, look at this.
I bleed oil when I take damage from this.
That's so annoying, so I start fires.
Like, what the hell?
Also, if I'm in water...
Can I make this even... hold on.
Oh, that's so annoying!
I need to remove the damage.
We can't have this.
Orbiting arc is a no-go.
I absolutely despise this, because it's gonna make me bleed oil and it removes all the water.
It's just a disaster.
Go up here.
Okay, damage field.
Gives a projectile an energy field that constantly deals... no, no, no, no, no, no.
Damage plus... wait.
Makes the projectile move considerably faster, but deals less damage.
Hey!
Wait a minute.
And then orbiting.
That way I cancel out the damage, but maybe it will give me healing still.
Oh, but it's too fast now.
Ah, fuck.
It's too fast.
Crab cakes.
Fuck, why is it so complicated to heal in this game?
I really don't want to have to go back up again.
I gotta have something here.
There's gotta be something.
Actually, hold on.
There's also spells below me.
Maybe some of this will do.
What's that?
Aim, aiming arc.
Heavy spreads.
I mean, I could just make... actually, hold on.
I have an idea.
We should just make a machine gun one and then I just stand in water and shoot up.
Just shoot like 20 at a time and then just quickly grab them.
That's actually not a bad idea.
Let me go back up here, because I can't stand the electricity sound.
Uh, we're gonna machine gun the shit out of this now.
I'll be borrowing from the... actually, hold on.
Give me the reduced recharge one.
Where's it there?
Okay, so we're limited by recharge time?
Let's steal one chainsaw.
Wait, what?
Oh, uh, Gamma's gonna affect that one.
Oh, yes!
Oh,
oh no, wait, wait.
Why am I... Oh, get rid of that, you idiot.
No, I ruined it.
Fuck.
I gotta go to another holy mountain.
I ruined it.
But it works now, look.
It's a machine gun healing.
I just need a very nice way to... what is it?
Warp cast?
What's that?
Makes a spell immediately jump a long distance, stopped by walls.
Uh, no.
It's almost there, boys.
I almost got it.
Honestly, it's already quite good.
If I can find something that reduces the projectile speed, then we got it.
And we really got it.
Something that where I don't need to stand in water, you know?
I just said a quick word in that context, but it sounded right in my mind.
What else do we have going for us?
I mean, if we go up to the surface, I guess, and we just shoot up...
Oh, but wait, it expires after a while, right?
So it may not necessarily come back down.
God, fucking... Why does orbiting fucking have damage on it?
That's so annoying.
But actually, wait a minute, maybe it's okay.
If we don't need to stand in water, right?
Hold on, we may be okay here.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Let's say I stand over here, and I just go orbiting.
Yeah!
And we're gonna bleed a lot, but who cares?
Look at that!
Fuck yeah, I did it!
That's totally okay for now.
We're gonna fix it and make it better later, but for now...
We got it.
Okay, cool.
The healing has been achieved.
That was a tough one.
Okay, stop slipping!
Thanks.
Ah, but now I can't edit.
Now I want to use... Tau, I guess.
Actually, wait a minute, let me just quickly check something.
Some of these spells actually contain stuff like projectile speed changes.
See, that one actually increases or reduces projectile speed a little bit.
You know, that's what I mean.
So if I can find a spell like that, that does something similar.
I can make it even better with what I have, maybe.
Wait a minute.
Uh,
wait.
Okay, stupid question, but check this out.
So a healing bolt does minus nine damage.
This is totally not gonna work, but imagine.
What if I take a spark bolt that has three damage, I apply this to it, reduces damage by minus 15, so does that heal me for 12?
Say what?
There's no way, right?
Uh, oh wait, I can't hit myself with that.
Um, what should I use?
Maybe.
No.
No, but maybe I can actually reduce the damage from the orbiting arc at least.
Uh, put this back.
Uh, hold on.
This one here.
Oh, I still take damage.
Wait, no, no.
No, wait, wait, what?
Why doesn't that work anymore?
Wait, why did that work before?
Wait a minute.
What the fuck?
Wait, why did that?
Huh?
That's fucking confusing.
Hold on.
Uh, put it here, I guess.
No, I still take damage.
So minus plus three, minus 15.
How does this not do zero damage to me now?
Let's put that there.
No, I do hate the fucking oil.
I'm not gonna lie here.
No, that's weird, man.
I mean, it works.
It works.
Let's not look at gift toys in the mouth.
It's already quite good.
Let me just double check my thing works.
Who?
Right.
Light shot.
I forgot I put that on there.
Also, is this one still?
Wait, what the fuck?
Oh, I forgot about the end.
That's amazing.
Uh, I'll keep one up here, I guess.
Actually, I don't need to do that.
Put these here.
Uh, put this up here.
Put this one on.
This is my storage wand, I guess, at this point.
Let me just get rid of some stuff I don't need ever.
At least I think so.
Two turns of wounded enemy into stone.
See, now it's very inaccurate.
Is that because of that one?
Wait a minute.
Why is it so inaccurate now?
Oh, we're missing the spark bolts, of course.
I'm an idiot.
Here.
Much better.
It is a little bit too slow now, though.
That makes that too slow.
Can we make it even slower with this, maybe?
No, because it's not Castellae we're dealing with.
It is the other one.
Actually, it shoots just as fast.
It's just a little less damage, I guess.
And I'm gonna get rid of the energy orb.
What do I put in instead?
I don't even know.
Nah, I'm okay with the energy orb, I guess.
Actually, maybe this one.
That is 25.
Why does that cost just as much?
Wow, 25 extra almost feels like nothing here for some reason.
Okay, I definitely want to go grab the ad mana now.
This is fine.
That does work every time, right?
Actually, it should be on another wand.
I should put it on this wand.
Ah, but then all my spells.
Maybe I say fuck the spells.
Throw them in here.
Honestly, I don't want any of these, I think.
Ah, wait, wait.
This one could come in handy.
That one.
What if I do this?
Whoops.
Hey!
I guess it's not bad.
I mean, I can still heal myself with it.
It's totally okay.
But it is a little bit less predictable.
God, I hate this electricity so much.
If I could, I would get rid of that perk.
Not even to get another one, just to get rid of it.
I would do it.
I am so tired of that sound.
I can't even tell you.
Yeah, we need a chainsaw on that.
I don't know why it works.
Oh, wait a minute.
Spells cast is two.
That's why it works like that.
Never mind, I understand.
That makes a lot of sense.
Yeah, there it is.
Do I want petrify though?
Probably not.
I really hate that I can't change my spells on the go.
But I have healing, I have black hole.
Healing black hole, and then I have a want for whatever.
I'll get rid of... stop.
Oh, get up here.
There we go.
Four spells, null shot.
There, throw this away.
All right, let's go.
I'm happy.
Actually, now I want to go to... Oh, hold on, hold on.
You know what?
Maybe I am happy with the setup actually.
We don't need the healing.
We have healing.
Healing is good.
So now I'm going to go up and grab the music wand.
Yep, we're doing that.
Actually, no, we're not.
We're doing that next time.
Actually, I'm going to stop here.
It's been a long time.
And we are in a good place.
We have black hole, healing, damage.
Next time we're going to do the wand with the music and we're
that was successful.
I would say that's very successful.
Huh?
Not bad.
I mean, it was okay.
Yes, subjective term.
Yeah.
I guess so.
In my book at least, I got somewhere, you know?
I solved some problems that I had.
In fact, I did a lot.
I killed the Yalchemisti.
I got the spells.
I went to Wand Mart.
I got some more spells and I made a black hole wand, healing wand.
I improved my damage wand.
Remember when I started today, my damage wand sucked.
It was super slow.
Didn't do anything.
Made it amazing.
Definitely set myself up.
A safe backup just in case you are completely right.
Holy shit.
Thanks for pointing that out.
Now, I just need to remember where exactly it's located.
Somewhere in app data.
Local low, I think.
Knowledge games noise.
Yeah, there it is.
Found it.
That has now been copied over.
Let's remove the last one.
Done.
Oh, safety.
I was 28 HP.
Yeah, it was rough.
But I did the right thing going back, playing safe.
I think the invisibility helped me a lot too in those situations.
Chad would not call that successful.
Ah, that's fine.
All that matters is what I call successful, right?
At some point, I'll reach the levels of Chad.
I have yet to attain this godly knowledge though.
You don't know the pain you caused us?
I honestly, I get a sick satisfaction knowing that maybe some people will get mad over certain way I do things.
It's not schadenfreude or anything.
I don't know.
It's just kind of hilarious, you know.
Your vibe based spell experimentation is exquisite and then a burnt stove emoji.
Honestly, I like the vibes.
The vibes are good.
That one run with infinite circle of vigors was pretty good.
Yeah.
That's what I really wanted to find.
Circle of vigor.
That is the ultimate healing.
And I had it on a black hole too.
The perfect setup for what I was doing that time.
I was going to the east.
And you take damage going through all that cursed rock.
But that black hole plus healing combo kept me at full health at all times.
Chad thinks anything short of the precise optimal game is not successful.
I guess so.
Chad is an amalgamation.
There are probably people that know less than you.
I mean, yeah, it's always a balance.
You know, there's people in the camp that have probably never played this game watching right now.
Maybe, who knows?
And then there's the experts.
At one point, I had...
I actually forgot his name now.
Fury.
Something.
Fury slam.
He was in here and he's like a neuter expert, right?
And then there were people that had never played the game.
So it's from all camps.
So you're right in saying that it's an amalgamation.
It's a bit of everything.
Fury forged.
That's right.
Yeah.
Fury forged.
Is it still blind since you watched the video on music notes?
I guess so.
I mean, it's like outside of the game knowledge, right?
The only way to truly play games blind is to be... is to start a game right after you're born when you're a empty tabula rasa, you know?
I don't know how to say that in English.
An empty plate, empty tablet, actually.
No, I came and the stream is ending.
Hope you had a fun today.
Dude, I had so much fun because I didn't die.
I nailed it today.
Well, by my standards.
I had a lot of fun.
Snake Gregory also watched you and some other noises streamers too.
Yeah, actually, I remember rating him a couple of times and he also rated my stream.
Dunk or slam.
That's right.
Yeah, there are some real noise to experts out there.
Newborns are called empty tablets.
Yeah, you know what I mean.
Tabula rasa.
Haven't you heard that expression?
Blank slate.
That's it.
Thoughts on the Poland man.
Poland is killing me in real life and in games.
Confirmed worst enemy of all time.
Did you get a chance to look at the emotes I post?
Actually, I didn't.
Let me do that now.
Let's see here.
They're all 7 TV emotes, right?
There is actually a way to add a bunch at the same time, I think, on 7 TV.
Oh yeah, I already like them.
The first one is amazing.
Is there a... Guys, is there a way to quickly add emotes here?
Or do I have to go on 7 TV and do things?
Maybe you don't know that.
I don't know.
Add emotes.
Well, I'm gonna add them for next time.
Count on it.
Unless there's something that, of course, breaks a rule or something.
Like something sexual or something.
I don't think there is, but you know, just saying.
I heard Poland and was a bit confused.
Yeah, it's all in Poland.
Am I saying that right, Poland?
Doesn't Poland want to be collected and spread?
So why does it try to kill us?
Is it stupid?
Frank is asking the real questions here.
There isn't about to overcook emote I saw today.
Really?
Which one is that?
Time to watch the Stanley Parable video.
Yeah, enjoy it.
That game is amazing.
I'm having a blast with it.
But I'm also constantly mind fucked.
And the crazy thing is, it's like the game can read my mind.
Have you made a rate message that explains why you drop us off and leave quickly?
I don't think I have.
I didn't even know I could do that.
Can I make a rate message?
What?
Is that a thing?
That's news to me.
I should finally play Stanley Parable myself now before watching it.
Yeah, you should.
It's really fun.
I recommend it.
Been a while.
Well, something to copy and paste.
Oh, I see what you mean.
Is it because the people are expecting me to be there?
I'm actually not sure.
I mean, we can try.
I mean, I usually just rate a channel and then that's it.
You know, people expect at least a message.
Oh, okay.
What should I say?
Oh, really?
Oh, I can just say like, okay, so I rated you, but I'm not actually reading chat.
So yeah, have fun.
You know, stuff like that.
Okay, good stuff.
Thanks actually for saying that to me.
Ah, okay.
Thanks for saying that.
Babbet Raven Warrior and Ducky Bird.
That's actually good to know.
I'm gonna do that now then.
I'm gonna end here anyway.
Guys, thank you so much for watching.
And I want to thank, of course, Mindscent.
You subscribed for three months at tier one.
That's four hours ago, though.
Probably not here anymore, but thank you anyway.
And a cat marionette an hour ago.
Thank you for subscribing for a single month.
I appreciate it.
Mindscent!
There you are.
So you are here.
Good to see you.
Thank you, man.
I'm gonna rate someone and let's, I'm gonna send a message.
Okay.
Let's see who's, of course, it's gotta be...
Guys, one of my all-time favorite or like dreams would be to rate someone like day nine and have him be like, acknowledge me, you know?
But I think he's too big.
We're gonna wait a bit.
I'm gonna rate same category.
Let's see who's dreaming neuter.
Someone first time playing grass urine.
Let's go for it.
I'm gonna send a message in their chat as well, letting them know.
Guys, thanks for watching.
I'll see you in the next video slash live stream or on Discord.
Have a good one.
Bye bye.